<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<locale fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="18" language="English">
   <text id="og_quest_3_3">It was not easy to catch them, and at some point a doubt crept in – can I handle it? My persistence has been rewarded – the rare species of these parts are no longer endangered, and will be protected in the reserve.</text>
   <text id="str_new_fish_win_layer">NEW SPECIES</text>
   <text id="quest_9_7_1">Buy the Spinning spoonbait!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_10_desc">A fisherman is going to part with his secret map of a hidden creek, if we manage to surpass his fishing mastery!</text>
   <text id="str_location_lochhness">The smell of autumn leaves fills the air, while a thick mist covers the water's surface. We have no idea what challenges face us brave fishermen in this mysterious lake. Who knows, maybe you will be the one to solve the secret of the mythical monster?</text>
   <text id="str_weight_lbs"> lbs</text>
   <text id="str_energy3_descr">Adds energy and allows for catching fish 20 percent larger</text>
   <text id="quest_7_1_2">Catch some fish weighing 5 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_12_8_3">You'll also need some Gold to pay for the journey!</text>
   <text id="str_inventory_title" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Inventory</text>
   <text id="str_fish_bersh_descr">Volga zander are common zander relatives differing from them by the following: smaller sizes, absence of canine teeth on the mandible and the pre-operculum is fully covered by scale. Volga zander are generally freshwater fish residing in lower reach of rivers. Their basic food is carp and perch fingerling. Volga zanders longer than 15cms feed on solely fish. Due to the lack of canine teeth they are unable to snatch and swallow large prey (because of narrow their throat).</text>
   <text id="halloween_4"> Fine Line </text>
   <text id="str_najivka_chafer">They say there is nothing better for catching perch than this small insect!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_verhoglyad">Sky Gazer</text>
   <text id="quest_7_3_2">Use the Grub lure.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_ugor">Freshwater Eel</text>
   <text id="quest_1_1_2">Use the Chopped Worm! The lure makes it easier to catch… anything in this river!	</text>
   <text id="quest_9_10_2">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total! You'll need something to eat during the journey!</text>
   <text id="str_mandarine_descr">Holiday lure designed for winter fish catching.</text>
   <text id="quest_10_5_1">Catch some Yellowcheeks!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_1_1">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_lenok_descr">Their body shape slightly resembles whitefish, but don't let it trick you, they are full-fledged Siberian trout! Their diet consists of insect larvae, earthworms and clams.</text>
   <text id="str_location_block">To unlock complete %d more achievements, on %s location.</text>
   <text id="quest_10_2_3">Catch some fish weighing 5 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc0_descr_8">Catch Tench on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_lineika_descr">Now you don't need to carry a measuring tape to blow your own horn about the size of the biggest fish you catch! And once dried, this fish will help you to save on school supplies for your kid.</text>
   <text id="str_update_error">Network Error!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_11">Lucky Bite - Catch any fish at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_11_4_3">Catch the leaf for the Uncle's herbarium!</text>
   <text id="og_quest_1_5">The giant creature had been fooling the locals for several weeks. Every now and then, its vague silhouette was seen in the murky waters, yet no one could catch that monster. But for me, the situation wouldn’t have changed! I pitched in!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_5_2">Catch some Sabrefish.</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_place">PLACE</text>
   <text id="quest_7_4_desc">A laboratory studying Ciscos asks you to catch some from different habitats!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_nublsimpl">Sp. Nubler Simple</text>
   <text id="victory_day_9">	Heavy artillery	</text>
   <text id="victory_day_10_3">	Catch fish for a certain total weight	</text>
   <text id="quest_14_2_3">Catch fish weighing 9 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer15">You can unlock Fish details by catching the fish or purchasing it for Gold.
    </text>
   <text id="str_fish_grayling">Grayling are close relatives of salmon and whitefish. They inhabit clear cold water rivers and lakes, preferring reservoirs with pebbles and stony bottoms. Grayling can have fluvial, fluvio-limnetic and pure limnetic forms. The trademark of a grayling is its large flag-like dorsal fin, which is embroidered with a pattern of spots and stripes. Graylings are omnivores. Their regular food is bottom dwelling organisms - gammarus, shell-fish, larvae and other forms of water metamorphosing insects</text>
   <text id="str_comics0">I'm so sick and tired of all this fuss…</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc11_descr_4">Catch Lenoks: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_daily_bonus_take">Get bonus</text>
   <text id="new_year_11">	Let's Decorate the Christmas Tree!	</text>
   <text id="quest_12_4_2">Catch an Arctic Grayling weighing 1.1 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_12_1_3">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="quest_15_7_desc">Locals have a tradition of decorating their bars with this fish. I smell a good opportunity to earn some money! </text>
   <text id="quest_8_9_desc">It is rumoured that some rods there are more convenient to use than others!</text>
   <text id="halloween_6"> Sinister creature </text>
   <text id="quest_8_7_desc">The National Zoo asks you to catch some particular fishes!</text>
   <text id="str_check_net1">Haul up your net - it's full of fish!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_3_desc">It's time to test our equipment on the new place!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_7_desc">A lab asks you to catch some Nases from different habitats!</text>
   <text id="str_send">Send</text>
   <text id="quest_2_5_1">Catch a Skygazer weighing 0.5 kg.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_2">Wildwood Master - Get all achievements on Wildwood Pool</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_spining_caplia_descr">A cheap spinning lure for rookie anglers. Its benefits are lightness and compactness. As for disadvantages, its spinning lacks durability and is not designed to carry a heavy reel. </text>
   <text id="quest_3_8">Championship</text>
   <text id="quest_10_4_2">Cast yout line several times!</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question0">What is this game about?
    </text>
   <text id="quest_11_9">Moving Out</text>
   <text id="new_year_5_desc">	We need to try hard for Honey Shore inhabitants not to be left without Christmas!	</text>
   <text id="halloween_3_1"> Catch some Thornies! </text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_1">Skilled Fihserman - Get all achievements on Honey Shore</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_super_middler1000">Sp. Bear Light</text>
   <text id="new_year_11_2">	Send some silver on delivering ball-fish to various locations!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc14_descr_5">Catch Drytails on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_13_4_3">Silver spent on purchases will be used for making new bells!</text>
   <text id="str_policy_text8">We have put in place reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to overcome those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. Also please note that email and messaging systems are not considered secure, so we discourage you from sending us personal information through these mediums. </text>
   <text id="quest_14_7_3">Catch some Carps in the Mountain Lake!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_leech">For agile and voracious predators like grass pike you should always take leech, that's for sure!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_round_goby_imp">Round goby are a benthic species preferring lightly-salted coastal areas of seas with a depth of 10-17 ft, but they also inhabit rivers, reservoirs and lakes. They are notable for their immensely broad range of adaptation abilities. Round goby can survive in areas of low oxygen and possess the advanced ability to respire through their skin. They prefer solid stony ground but may be found on shell, sand or even muddy ground. They can obtain nutrition from a wide reange of sources, but their basic food is shell-fish, crustaceans and water plants. </text>
   <text id="quest_11_3_3">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="new_year_12">	Elf-fish	</text>
   <text id="quest_7_4">Whitefish Research</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_zelen">Alga</text>
   <text id="str_fish_arovana">Silver arowana</text>
   <text id="quest_13_8_1">Cast your line several last times on the Northern Donets!</text>
   <text id="str_server_gold_descr">Your appeal in support was considered. Take as compensation this set of gold coins. Enjoy the game!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc9_descr_3">Catch Yellowcheeks: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_9_7_desc">A world-famous spoonbait producer has modified its product and asks you to test it!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_skalp_desc"> A cheaper equivalent of perch spoon. A bit of wit and even a scalpel can be a real spoon! </text>
   <text id="str_exit_title">Exit from game</text>
   <text id="str_fish_speedy_descr">Representatives of the carp family. Not a fussy species - they'll eat almost anything; insects are their favorite breakfast. Although they are not marketable fish, they are often used as bait for catching larger, predatory fish.</text>
   <text id="og_quest_2_8">How much may depend upon one man’s determination to do good? This fundraising campaign to protect local fauna started with my small donation, but it attracted public attention, and now the nature of these lands will be saved!</text>
   <text id="str_tutorial_comics_text8">	Change the lure to catch a fish quicker!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc3_descr_0">Catch Tube Nosed Gobys: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_5_7">Chin-wagging Farmer</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_fb_desc2">We will never post anything to your wall without your permission.</text>
   <text id="quest_7_6_1">Catch several Shads.</text>
   <text id="quest_2_8_1">Catch Bersches weighing at least 0.8 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_fry">Medium-sized predators, for instance, such as eel or pike like smaller fish. But to catch these fish for bait you have to be as good as them!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc2_descr_5">Catch Snakeheads: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_6_3_2">Use the Sugar lure!</text>
   <text id="new_year_1_1">	Catch some fish with Santa and listen to his story!	</text>
   <text id="new_year_10_1">	Catch an icy fish weighing 3.5 kg!	</text>
   <text id="quest_3_10_1">Catch Burbot weighing a specific total.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_bream">Bream are shy and smart fish, who stick together in small groups, often in the depths among thick algae. They are very tasty when fried or baked, but extremely bony, so be careful when eating them.</text>
   <text id="victory_day_11_1">	Catch the two major Fish Generals weighing not less than 0.7 kg.	</text>
   <text id="quest_3_4_3">Catch a rare herb sample!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_blue_bream">Blue bream  are river-lake fish. You will hardly ever find them in stillwater lakes and fast moving mountain rivers as they prefer silent stretches in large rivers and running lakes situated in river beds. Crustaceans, insects, worms and plants are the staple diet of adult blue bream.</text>
   <text id="quest_8_8_3">The 3d rule: Catch some Verkhovkas weighing 8 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_6_2">Catch some Royal Fish in the Victory River!</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_stew_descr">Canned stew meat can be stored long-term. It can be used not only for eating, but also as a perfect feed. </text>
   <text id="quest_bonus_1_2">	Catch 2 fish weighing at least 0.1 kg each!	</text>
   <text id="quest_14_5_desc">The National Zoo asks you to catch some rare local fish!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_beloglazka">White Eye</text>
   <text id="str_fb_messages_top_label">Help your friends to unlock new fishingspots!</text>
   <text id="str_remaining">Remaining</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc9_descr_8">Catch Soldatov's Catfish at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="str_rod_broken">Your rod is broken!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_hlebnii_myakish">Breadcrumb</text>
   <text id="quest_4_9_2">Catch some Basses on the Honey Coast!</text>
   <text id="str_get">Get</text>
   <text id="str_policy_head">Privacy Policy</text>
   <text id="quest_6_10_2">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="quest_5_9_2">Catch Cisco weighing a specific total.</text>
   <text id="quest_8_8_1">The 1st rule: Catch as much fish as you can!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_baikal_grayling">Baikal grayling feed on mainly caddis worms and adult caddis, stoneflies, scuds, or goby spawns during spawning time. They are very active fish. When moving up a river for spawning Baikal grayling can overcome rapid currents and even whirlpools. While hunting for flying insects Baikal grayling are able to jump up to half a metre out of the water.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_dorado">Dorado</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_longx_desc">Reliable classic model of Longlass class. Greater ring thickness provides additional durability. Large fish weighing 25 kg - the dream of any respectable fisherman come true!</text>
   <text id="str_spin_chance">Increased chance of the SuperPrize</text>
   <text id="quest_4_1">Otherworldly Beauty</text>
   <text id="halloween_1_1"> Catch a few hell-fish! </text>
   <text id="quest_9_6_2">Catch some Riffle Minnows!</text>
   <text id="entity_gold_coin_title">	Gold coin	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_artrodir">Arthrodira</text>
   <text id="str_policy_text6">We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on the Service. We do not provide any personal information to third-party advertising companies on a non-aggregate basis. Our system and the third-party advertising technology may use aggregate information, non-personal information, Drimmi's cookies on your hard drive and your use of the Service to target advertisements. In addition, advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on other sites. If advertisements are served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed on your computer. Similarly, third-party advertising companies may provide us with pixel tags (also called clear gifs or beacons) to help manage and optimize online advertising. Beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits the site on which is beacon is located, and to learn which banner ads bring users to a given site. </text>
   <text id="quest_10_8_desc">Local fishermen have got a picture of an incredible fish! We must catch it!</text>
   <text id="str_location_morskaya">Open Sea</text>
   <text id="str_ok">OK</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer1">You have to visit a lot of picturesque fishing spots! Complete quests, net fish, sell your catch and share your achievements with friends! Find new places for fishing to become a real professional of fishing!
    </text>
   <text id="str_fish_gorchak_descr">Bitterling is a fish with high laterally compressed body and large scales. Bitterling ordinary prefers ponds with stagnant or low flowing water. It feeds mostly with vegetarian diet: conferva, algae (diatoms), that is why, probably, its flesh has a bitter taste.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_stone_loach">Stone loach live a abottom dwelling life. They prefer quite small fast-flowing rivers with a sandy or pebble bottom, but may be found in lower reaches of large rivers, lakes, salted waters of the Gulf of Finland, reservoirs and ponds. Stone loach burrow in silt for the winter, they are able to survive for a long time by staying in in wet ground after reservoirs have dried up. Stone loach feed on water invertebrates, insect larvae, plants and fish spawn.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc4_descr_9">Catch Carp at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_2_8_desc">A local Bersch Protection Fund asks for help!</text>
   <text id="str_policy_head6">Third-Party Advertising Companies</text>
   <text id="str_fish_arovana_descr">They say this fish can understand human language and posses penetrating minds. Any aquarist dreams of having at least one beautiful arowana in their tank. Don't fry the arowanas, give them to good cooks instead.</text>
   <text id="quest_11_1_1">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_ygor_descr">Eels' release electric charges, their fiercest weapon, so be careful. Any attempt to catch these eels is like taking a bath with electricity!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_svyaz_descr">	Master of underwater communications, able to provide a signal in the most troubled waters.	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc11_descr_2">Catch Omuls: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_10_3_2">Earn some silver!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_dogfish">Takifugu rubripes</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_coins"> Coin </text>
   <text id="str_faq_question14">How can I catch the fish I need?
    </text>
   <text id="quest_12_3_2">Catch some Arctic Ciscos!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_3_2">Catch some Roaches!</text>
   <text id="str_shop_gold_bonus">Bonus</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_ends_in">Ends in</text>
   <text id="new_year_7_3">	Catch some fish weighing 7 kg in total.	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc_tut_descr_0">Catch Perch at least [weight] </text>
   <text id="victory_day_8_2">	Catch some Guerrilla-Fish.	</text>
   <text id="quest_12_8">Moving Out</text>
   <text id="str_terms_head5">Privacy and Protection of Personal Information</text>
   <text id="victory_day_9_1">	Catch some Gunner-Fish to raise a unit.	</text>
   <text id="str_shop_gold">gold coins</text>
   <text id="str_quest_53_text">This season's special is grilled [fish type]! If you catch [total weight] it will be perfect!</text>
   <text id="new_year_16_2">	Catch ball-fish weighing 0.8 kg.	</text>
   <text id="quest_7_6_3">Catch several Shads weighing 3 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="str_location_seq_block">To unlock complete all quests at previous location</text>
   <text id="str_fish_conger_eel">Conger eels differ from freshwater eel by their longer dorsal fin, complete absence of scales and their large size. Conger eels are voracious predators eating mainly small and medium-sized fish. Their mighty teeth easily crush mollusc shells. There are eyewitnesses who have seen conger eel tearing trapped fish out of nets. Their preferable habitats are rocky coasts where they hide somewhere in an underwater cave or crevasse and surprise their victims. Conger eels dig holes in sandy bottoms like river eels sometimes do.</text>
   <text id="quest_2_8_3">Silver spent on purchases will go to the Fund!</text>
   <text id="str_daily_bonus_tFriend">Tell a friend</text>
   <text id="quest_2_6_3">Catch some Bitterlings weighing at least 0.2 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_0_title" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="26">Power of lure</text>
   <text id="quest_10_1_desc">Here we are! Just look, how bautiful this place is! Let's cast the line now!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_jivec_descr">Imitating shy whitebait, this lure moves jerkily from side to side. Any large predator will start chasing such easy meat right off bat - and will receive a shock! </text>
   <text id="str_fish_barb">Barb feed on mainly bottom dwelling organisms: shell-fish, worms, larvae and crustaceans. The distinctive features of a barb include two pairs of barbells at the corners of its mouth and head that aid in finding food on the river bed. Recently, the barb population has significantly decreased as a result of intensive fishing and pollution. Barb caviar is toxic.</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_oparish">Maggots</text>
   <text id="quest_3_9_2">Use the Spoon spoonbait.</text>
   <text id="quest_8_4_2">Catch some Verkhovkas weighing at least 0.9 kg.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_lenok">Lenok</text>
   <text id="str_fish_baikal_harius">Baikal Grayling</text>
   <text id="str_amulet_title">With amulet all fish will be bigger! Forever!</text>
   <text id="str_fb_text4">This one was something! But now it's my personal pride!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_6_1">Catch some Pirate Basses!</text>
   <text id="victory_day_4_1">	Catch some Signalfish to form a signal detachment!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc8_descr_8">Catch Atlantic sturgeon at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="og_open_honey_shore">After the stunning success on the Forest River, we were not going to rest on our laurels. Two days later, we were made to feel welcome in Honey Beach – the locals, who had heard a lot about our feats, were ready to render us all sorts of assistance.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_shipovka_descr_imp">Chipper is a small river fish, the largest specimens of chipper are rarely longer than 4 inches. And females are larger than males. This fish color is mottled but not bright, the basic tone is gray, light yellow or brown, on which are scattered small dark spots. It lives exclusively in clean waters. Chipper eats small invertebrates. Chipper prefers sandy-clayey soil, in which it can easily hide itself.</text>
   <text id="quest_7_5_3">Catch a rusty can!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_6_1">Catch 2 Tenches.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc7_descr_4">Catch Siberian Graylings: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_8_10_3">You'll also need some Gold to pay for the journey!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_super_bear">Professional tackle of the &quot;Bear&quot; series, best rod on the market! The price is moderated by high quality and reliability - titan rod will never break. Allows you to catch any fish, without weight limit!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_6">Question of Life</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_choco_descr">Holiday bait designed for winter fish catching.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_trairao_descr">Strong, active predators. Their jaws make a dangerous weapon. They like large spaces and water reservoirs. Small fish, mollusks, shrimps and other shellfish are their favorite delicacies. We advise to stock up with more of those before fishing!</text>
   <text id="str_event_day">d.</text>
   <text id="quest_8_3">Schmindler's List</text>
   <text id="quest_4_9">Urgent Research</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_blesna_cherviak">Worm</text>
   <text id="quest_12_2_3">Catch more fish than the forester!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_3_3">Catch some Blue Breams weighing 0.8 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_10">Away into Sunset</text>
   <text id="quest_7_7_3">Catch some Taimens!</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_leaderboard">Leaderboard</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc5_descr_9">Catch Catfish at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="victory_day_9_desc">	Underwater battle is lost, and river general swims sadly near the shore. At the last moment a brilliant idea appears – the gunners can reverse the trend! But where to find them..?	</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_suhariki">Crackers</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_okun">Perch</text>
   <text id="str_fish_bottle_descr"> Very rare member of bottle family. It can be found in waters with low content of hops, the degree of which does not exceed 15% </text>
   <text id="quest_11_1">Test Casting</text>
   <text id="entity_accelerator_progress_title">	Catch scale up	</text>
   <text id="str_fishlist_razdelitel_0">Common</text>
   <text id="halloween_8_desc"> Although the Amur catfish does not have the bright aggressive features, it is an inexpressible hidden threat! </text>
   <text id="str_fish_cisco">Ciscos inhabit cold oxygen-rich northern waters. They are not timind and need no speical care while fishing, especially in deep rivers and lakes. You should use caution around ciscos, as they feed on prey moving in schools and excessive splashing may scare away other species.</text>
   <text id="str_quest_completed">Quest completed</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_dragonfly">If you want to catch something larger than a ruff, the dragonfly is a good choice! Fishermen say that lake trout love dragonflies.</text>
   <text id="quest_10_6_2">Catch some Penalfish weighing 4 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_location">On location</text>
   <text id="str_fish_okun_pirat">Pirate Perch</text>
   <text id="quest_6_5_1">Use the Nubler Smart rod.</text>
   <text id="og_open_sand_valley">The deceptive lifelessness of this place couldn’t deter me. The quiet but deep waters were swarming with life, and my rivals knew it – the shore was full of those who wanted to try their luck.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_pint_descr"> Sometimes even the most experienced fishermen among the tranquil waters dreams about pint of refreshing drink.. JoyPint incredibly similar to the outlines of the mug! </text>
   <text id="str_fish_oscar">Oscar</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_new_year_descr">	You can found this incredible Ice Rod in the shop only on Christmas holidays. Though its origin is unknown, all real fishermen will be glad to purchase it!	</text>
   <text id="halloween_7_2"> Catch arthrodiras at least 37 kg! </text>
   <text id="str_spin_gold">Spin</text>
   <text id="quest_4_5_3">Catch some Silver Crucians!</text>
   <text id="str_tired_fish_title">Time to win</text>
   <text id="quest_14_5_1">Catch some Channel Catfish!</text>
   <text id="quest_11_4_desc">Here we can find a rare leaf for the Uncle's herbarium!</text>
   <text id="str_comics_tap_the_screen">Tap the screen</text>
   <text id="quest_12_1_desc">It's so calm and silent here! Fishing there must be a delight!</text>
   <text id="halloween_5"> Fear color </text>
   <text id="quest_4_10_desc">I've found out there is a beautiful lake in nearby mountains... I wish I could see it!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_5_desc">It's time to replenish our stocks: we won't be able to catch anything without equipment!</text>
   <text id="new_year_16_3">	Catch ball-fish weighing 10 kg in total!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_pint">JoyPint</text>
   <text id="str_policy_text9">The Service is not geared toward children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information we will delete such information from our files as quickly as possible. </text>
   <text id="str_fish_goldfish_descr">Gold fish are blazing lake fish eating various invertebrates, water plankton and algae. Their sparkling gold-orange scale delights our eyes.</text>
   <text id="halloween_7"> Evil fins </text>
   <text id="quest_4_1_2">Catch fish weighing 1 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="quest_9_1_2">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_fb_inv_fr_message">Invite friends and play with them!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_2">Strength of Faith</text>
   <text id="str_fish_olivk_som">Olive Catfish</text>
   <text id="quest_11_6_desc">National Zoo workers are amazed at the number of rare species inhabiting this area and ask you to catch more for them!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_4">Herb Expert</text>
   <text id="str_fish_ice">Ice fish</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc0_descr_2">Catch Gudgeon: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_tutorial_comics_text6">	You're doing great! Now let's sell our catch!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc7_descr_2">Catch Upswimers: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_3_6_2">Catch some Mudfish!</text>
   <text id="og_open_loch_ness">A weird being was staring at me out of the water. I could barely make a couple of steps towards it when it disappeared into the murky depths of the lake. My heart was pounding – just a few moment before I had a chance encounter with the legendary Loch Ness monster!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_2_desc">	Don't forget that a fisherman uses not only rods, but nets! Try and see how useful they are!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_pike">Pike are freshwater fish, sticking to water grasses at a certain depth in reservoirs. Adult pike enjoy a richly varied diet, which usually consists of a variety of fish species as well as mice, rats, curlews and squirrels crossing rivers. The largest pike are able to attack ducks. Pike meat is very tasty and good for people on a diet as it contains only 2-3% oil.</text>
   <text id="quest_6_10_1">Pay some gold to buy a map of the new area.</text>
   <text id="str_close">Close</text>
   <text id="str_fish_red_eye_imp">Red-eye are often confused with another fish species, i.e. roach, but experienced fishermen know that the former differ from the latter by numerous signs, no need to look inside or under gills.A red-eye's scale is finer and has a golden shade. Also, these fish are thicker and fleshier, similar to breach rather than roach. Larger red-eye (above 1.76 lbs) gain deeper red color, sometimes their scale is filled with bloody color.</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_kukuruza">Corn</text>
   <text id="str_fish_okun_pavlin_descr">The most aggressive members of the perch family. Can be recognized easily by the peacock's eye at the base of their tails. Highly valued by fishermen worldwide! These hunters can even catch a low flying bird in their jaws.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_chum">Chum are anadromous red fish, the largest and most abundant species of Pacific salmon. Chum are valuable commercial fish. They spawn once in a lifetime, embarking on an amazing journey from the Pacific waters to mountain river heads. After spawning, chum die on their way back. Chum salmon are considered to be champion jumpers when heading upstream to spawn.</text>
   <text id="quest_10_4_3">Catch the creature's head!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_belyi_amyr_descr">The white Amur is a purely phytovorous fish, feeding on aquatic plants. It is a commercial fish with a tasty, fatty meat, and is considered a valuable part of pond farming.</text>
   <text id="quest_9_1_3">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_5_desc">Let's contribute to the environmental protection and pull out an old rusty can from the water!</text>
   <text id="quest_9_3">Romance</text>
   <text id="str_fish_rotan">Rotan</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_vodorosli">Algae</text>
   <text id="quest_6_4_2">Catch a Ratan Goby weighing at least 0.7 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_6_desc">There is a Fishing championship coming up on Thousand Islands! We must win!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_10_1">Cast your line several last times on the Sand Ridge!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_3_2">Catch a rare lizard!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc5_descr_7">Catch [amount] Asps at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_fish_chub">Chub are freshwater fish in the carp family. They feed on various types of food and are omnivores. Their food consists of insects, shell-fish, crayfish, frogs, fish spawn and fingerlings, as well as anything which falls into the water, even cherries. Large chub are extremely voracious predators, they not only swallow a lot of gudgeon and bleak, but they also snap up anything else foolish enough to venture into the water, including mice.</text>
   <text id="quest_10_10_desc">Let's go towards the beautiful Amazon! I wish I could get there immediately!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_5_2">Catch an Amur Catfish weighing 3 kg.</text>
   <text id="str_amulet_info_1">Silver Amulet: Gives 15% increase to the weight of the catch!</text>
   <text id="str_terms_text5">Information collected from you is subject to the pertinent social network's policy. By using the Service, you may be granting your social network permission to share your e-mail address and any other personally identifiable information with Drimmi LLC. Please see Drimmi LLC's Privacy Policy for more information on the collection and use of your information. You acknowledge and agree that the Privacy Policy is incorporated and made part of these Terms.</text>
   <text id="str_energy1">Simple tonic</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_title_list">Set net</text>
   <text id="str_fb_gift_message">%s helped you to unlock location</text>
   <text id="quest_7_1_1">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question20">Where can I get Gold?
    </text>
   <text id="str_market_rate">Rate</text>
   <text id="quest_2_5_desc">The National Park asks you to catch some local species!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_7_2">Use the Plastic rod.</text>
   <text id="str_notif2">Become a pro fisherman. Catch a rare catfish!</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_description">CATCH 10 BIGEST SALMON ON ISLE SHORE FISHINGSPOT</text>
   <text id="quest_10_5_3">Catch some Barbels!</text>
   <text id="str_spining_letter">S</text>
   <text id="quest_3_3_2">Catch some Amur Sleepers!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_ukleika">Bleak</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_nubler_h">An improved rod of the Nubler series. Using carbon as a material makes the tackle handy and allows you to catch fish weighing up to 3 kg.</text>
   <text id="quest_12_5_1">Catch some Arctic Chars!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc1_descr_4">Catch Bitterling: [amount]</text>
   <text id="new_year_13">	The Spirit of Christmas	</text>
   <text id="quest_15_3_desc">The brewer said there are incredible fish living in this lake! Let's have a look!</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_net3_descr"> Nets with cells 27-32 mm is usually used to catch medium-sized fish. In general these nets are designed for medium-sized herbivorous and omnivorous fish and small predators. Sometimes bigger fish can be caught with this net if it reels its tail into the net. </text>
   <text id="new_year_8">	Santa Fish!	</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_listia">Water Herbarium</text>
   <text id="str_loading" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Loading ...</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc5_descr_0">Catch Rotans: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_6_2">Bring the Fish!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_sea_lamprey">Sea lamprey are parasites. Their mouths are in the form of sucking discs with numerous keratose teeth. Using these teeth, sea lampreys stick to large fish - cod, flatfish, etc. The mouth produces chemicals to prevent the host's blood from clotting. The external slime of sea lamprey is toxic, so the most common way of cooking them is frying.</text>
   <text id="str_hour">hours</text>
   <text id="str_fish_tilapia_descr">Sea chick&quot;, &quot;River chicken&quot; - call them what you like! This popular fish has huge economic and industrial significance. Omnivorous.</text>
   <text id="quest_2_2_1">Catch some Gudgeons faster than Jessica.</text>
   <text id="quest_6_5_3">Catch a rusty can!</text>
   <text id="new_year_11_desc">	To make the Christmas Tree look really festively, we need lots of decorations!	</text>
   <text id="str_quest_reward">Quest Reward</text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_10">Hungry for Fish - Catch fish on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_restore">Restore</text>
   <text id="quest_10_3_3">Silver spent on purchases will go to the mirror-making plant!</text>
   <text id="quest_9_3_2">Catch a Zander weighing 1.2 kg!</text>
   <text id="og_quest_3_7">The work was performed flawlessly. Even the professor nodded approval when examining the samples. That meant that the lab had everything we needed to assess the environmental situation in the region. That also meant that I was about to receive a handsome reward!</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question3">How do I win a mini-game?
    </text>
   <text id="str_terms_text0">These Terms of Service (&quot;Terms&quot;) are a legal agreement between Drimmi LLC, its Affiliates (&quot;Drimmi LLC&quot; or &quot;we&quot;) and you (&quot;you&quot;). Affiliates shall mean subsidiaries, parent companies, joint ventures and other corporate entities under common ownership. By using or accessing any Drimmi LLC game or application (&quot;Service&quot;) you agree to be bound by these Terms. Drimmi's Privacy Policy is incorporated herein by reference. By accessing or using the Service, you agree that you have read, understood, and accept to be bound by the Terms. Drimmi LLC reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify or revise these Terms at any time, and you agree to be bound by such modifications or revisions. If you do not agree to the Terms, do not use the Service.                  Users are responsible for periodically viewing the Terms. Your continued use of the Service after a change or update has been made will constitute your acceptance to the revised Terms. If you do not agree to the Terms your only remedy is to discontinue your use of the Service and cancel any accounts you have made using the Service.                  If you violate the Terms, Drimmi LLC reserves the right to issue you a warning regarding the violation or immediately terminate or suspend any or all accounts you have created using the Service. You agree that Drimmi LLC need not provide you notice before terminating or suspending your account(s), but it may do so.                  Drimmi LLC reserves the right to refuse any user access to the Services without notice for any reason, including, but not limited to, a violation of the Terms.                  You agree that Drimmi LLC may discontinue the Service or change the content of the Service at any time, for any reason, with or without notice to you, without liability.                  You represent that you are 13 years old or older. If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, you represent that your legal guardian has reviewed and agrees to the Terms.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_malek">Small Fish</text>
   <text id="new_year_11_1">	Catch some ball-fish!	</text>
   <text id="str_buy">Buy</text>
   <text id="str_fish_shtrafbat">Battalion fish</text>
   <text id="str_fish_elf_descr">These funny creatures can be noticed not far from Santa-fishes in holiday time.</text>
   <text id="str_fb_messages_check_all">Check all</text>
   <text id="quest_2_2_2">Catch a Gudgeon weighing at least 0.13 kg.</text>
   <text id="quest_9_3_3">Catch fish weighing 8 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_earthworm">One of the most popular and simple baits for catching various young omnivorous fish. But it won't really help you catch something big.</text>
   <text id="str_inventory_equipped" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Used</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_zemnovodnie">Amphibians</text>
   <text id="quest_5_9_1">Catch some Cisco!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc6_descr_9">Catch Hucho Perryi at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_10_7_3">Catch fish weighing 5 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_3">Zoo</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_konfeta_descr">If you have been thinking that cakes cannot grow on trees or a perfect day for a banana-fish will never come, it's time to change your mind! This fish consists of sweet caramel that just melts in your mouth!</text>
   <text id="quest_9_4">Mystical Creature</text>
   <text id="str_fish_bersh">Volga Zander</text>
   <text id="quest_5_2_3">Silver spent on purchases will go to buy a cake for the farmer!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_vertuska">Spinner</text>
   <text id="new_year_18_desc">	Look, how happy they are — Christmas celebration went well! Let's organize a Christmas competition!	</text>
   <text id="str_location_fb_label">Ask your friends for help!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_8_2">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total! You'll need something to eat during the journey!</text>
   <text id="str_terms_head3">Virtual Currencies/Goods</text>
   <text id="quest_15_6_desc">Openerfish is very popular among locals. They are ready to pay for a catch of this wonderful fish!</text>
   <text id="str_tutorial_comics_text5">	To catch a fish, keep it inside the circle!	</text>
   <text id="quest_14_2_desc">Uncle Joe said that when he was young he could break any local fishing record! Hm, can we do the same now?</text>
   <text id="quest_9_6_1">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_2_desc">This fisherboy alleges he can catch fish better than you! Challenge accepted!</text>
   <text id="str_fb_request_text_ask">Please help me unlock locations</text>
   <text id="quest_15_1">Happy Brewer</text>
   <text id="str_fish_amer_som_descr">American Catfish is very unpretentious in food. The native habitat - fresh waters of North America, in the region of the Great Lakes of Florida. The difference between it and ordinary catfish is small size and presence of 4 pairs of barbels.</text>
   <text id="quest_4_5">Silver and Gold</text>
   <text id="str_fish_karp_descr_imp">Carp are large yellow-green and brown omnivorous fish, they have thick longish body covered by coarse, smooth, gold-green-grey-brown scale. Carp may live for 50 years or more. The average carp weighs 20 lbs, but it can reach 77 lbs. Carp eat almost without breaks because they belong to the group  of stomachless fish. They are called &quot;omnivore water spirits&quot; and resemble pigs in their lack of discrimination regarding food choice, as well as their rapid growth and gluttony.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_maybug">Chafer</text>
   <text id="str_policy_text1">Drimmi's primary objective in collecting user information is to provide and enhance the Service and to enable users to easily navigate and enjoy the Service.          When you install any of the Drimmi games or applications, we may collect and record the information you provide us voluntarily through www.facebook.com (&quot;Facebook&quot;) and/or other social network(s) in accordance with the policies and terms of Facebook and/or other social network(s).          The types of personal information collected in accordance with the activities listed above may vary depending on the activity. This &quot;personal information&quot; is defined as information about you that can be used to contact or identify you. Personal information may include: (1) your first and last name, (2) your profile picture or its URL, (3) your user identification number of the pertinent social network, which is linked to publicly available information such as name and profile picture (4) the login email you provided to the pertinent social network upon registration. Additionally, we may acquire information from you through (1) your access and participation in message boards on the Service (2) your email of a question to our customer support (3) your purchase of a virtual product of any type (4) other sources, including but not limited to newspapers and internet sources such as blogs, instant messaging services, other users of the Service to supplement your profile. Please note that because a third party site manages the purchases of virtual goods offered by the Service, we do not have access to your credit card details and billing information.          Drimmi may also invite you to share non-personal information about yourself which may include but is not limited to: (1) your age or date of birth; (2) your gender; (3) information about the hardware you may own; (4) your favorite websites, friend information (such as friends of yours that are also connected to our Service) and fan pages; (5) your physical location and that of your access device (collectively referred to as &quot;non-personal information&quot;). If non-personal information is collected for an activity that also requires personal information, Drimmi may combine your non-personal information with your personal information in an attempt to provide you with a better user experience, to improve the quality and value of the Services and to analyze how our Service is used.          The Service will also record game play information such as your high scores or game session duration.          In addition to information collected as described above, you may choose to share additional information about yourself throughout the Service, such as in games or on message boards. Any actions you perform with other players are considered public, and are at your sole discretion.          We may use your name, profile picture, email address and other information to notify you of new product releases, service notifications, and to solicit your feedback and input. Those emails will contain links for preference management and where appropriate, unsubscribe links should you decide you do not want to receive further emails.          Finally, any time you access the Service, we may collect aggregate information including but not limited to internet protocol addresses, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time of this activity (aggregate information). We use this aggregate information to better tailor the Service to your interests, to provide you more efficient customer support, and to overall enhance the Service.          We may use your name, profile picture and game play information to communicate with your friends that are also connected to the Service, which you can opt out by contacting us via email. We may also disclose information about you to our partners, such as our publisher Six Waves Inc., in order to provide the Service, resolve service problems and correct errors in the Service, to communicate with you about the Service, to provide you with advertising and promotional information in connection with the Service, and to enhance your experience on the Service. However, we do not give our partners an independent right to share this information. Due to our contractual obligations with these third parties and the need to share information to deliver and support the Service, we cannot provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of sharing information (whether personal information or non-personal information) with these third parties. Drimmi, certain of its partners, and each of their contractors and employees may view the information that you transmit to the Service to provide the Service and otherwise perform the tasks set forth in this Privacy Policy.          In all cases of data access and collection, the information you provide will not be disclosed, rented, leased, loaned, sold, or otherwise voluntarily distributed to unaffiliated third parties and will be used solely for the purpose of providing you with and improving the Service. </text>
   <text id="str_mandarine">Tangerines</text>
   <text id="str_terms_text7">By visiting or using the Service, you agree that the laws of Moscow, without regard to principles of conflict of laws and regardless of your location, will govern these Terms of Service and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Drimmi LLC. Any claim or dispute between you and Drimmi LLC that arises in whole or in part from your use of the Service shall be decided exclusively by a court of competent jurisdiction located in Moscow, and you hereby consent to, and waive all defenses of lack of personal jurisdiction and forum non conveniens with respect to venue and jurisdiction in Moscow. Drimmi LLC reserves the right to amend these Terms of Service at any time and without notice, and it is your responsibility to review these Terms of Service for any changes. Your use of Drimmi LLC following any amendment of these Terms of Service will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms. YOU AND Drimmi LLC AGREE THAT ANY CAUSE OF ACTION ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE SERVICE MUST COMMENCE WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES. OTHERWISE, SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION IS PERMANENTLY BARRED.</text>
   <text id="victory_day_11_desc">	The river general and his enemies are the real troublemakers! If you catch them – the river will live peacefully again – let's do it!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_general">General</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_elite2000_desc">You can't miss the enhanced Elite version, which deserves a particular attention! This cult spinning can catch fish weighing 40 kg.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_okun">Perch</text>
   <text id="quest_1_1_1">Buy the Chafer in the shop. No bait no fishing!	</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_brelki_descr">Sometimes you may catch something unexpected from the water! Here, for instance, are key fobs. Not only are they pretty objects, but the caught key could surprisingly open the door to a luxury car or a villa! </text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc4_descr_5">Catch Zonder on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_net1"> Quality usual net </text>
   <text id="quest_3_10_desc">We have to get on to the Sunset Coast! Let's prepare to the journey properly!</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_obuv">Boots and shoes</text>
   <text id="quest_6_4_1">Catch a Pike weighing at least 1.5 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_morskaya_minoga">Sea Lamprey</text>
   <text id="quest_7_8_1">Catch some Chum Salmon!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc14_descr_9">Catch [amount] JoyPint at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="quest_9_8">Zoo Order!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_5_1">Catch more Amur Catfish than the fisherman.</text>
   <text id="str_task_denom">	pcs.	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc0_descr_6">Catch Perch: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_1_7">Lucky Card</text>
   <text id="quest_13_1_1">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="str_athlas_collections_button">Collections</text>
   <text id="str_tutorial_comics_text_continue">	Continue	</text>
   <text id="og_catch_rare_fish">When the silhouette of this giant flickered at the lake surface, it was absolutely clear that I had to catch it even if it would be the last thing I would do in my life! Our fight lasted for two weeks. My opponent was strong, but my skill and backbone finally prevailed!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_1_2">Catch some Barbels!</text>
   <text id="quest_11_7_desc">We've stumbled upon a hungry native, who is ready to part with a pile of gold in exchange for freshly cooked fish soup!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_9_1">Catch fish weighing 8 kg in total: we'll need food during the journey!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc9_descr_1">Catch a Ribbon-shaped fish: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_15_5">Drytails</text>
   <text id="new_year_4_desc">	The citizens by themselves won't prepare for Christmas in time! Let's hurry up and help them!	</text>
   <text id="quest_14_6_3">Catch Lake Chars weighing 6 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_round_descr">	A festive bait, designed for catching Christmas fish.	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_pirapytanga_descr">River fish that like rocky riverbeds. When caught, their coloring changes to yellowish, making their previous silver shine disappear. Prefer fruits and other weeds for breakfast.</text>
   <text id="halloween_8"> The silent threat </text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_artelerist_descr">The new barrel-fish is a modern modification of the sword-fish! Its progress never stops, and the underwater world is also involved in gradual rearmament. This new upgraded 12.7-caliber cannoneer-fish fires up to 750 hatchlings per minute!</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question15">How can I unlock Fish details?
    </text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc1_descr_0">Catch Flat Bream: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_minoga">Lampern</text>
   <text id="quest_2_6_2">Catch some Bitterlings!</text>
   <text id="quest_11_3">Monsterfish</text>
   <text id="quest_2_2">Whose Rod Is Longer</text>
   <text id="quest_6_4_3">Catch a Ruff weighing at least 0.5 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_second_prize_description">Super super fishing rod</text>
   <text id="og_open_severskyi_donec">The impregnable monastery walls are towering white over me. I wonder if the sound of bells can scare away the fish... Let's check it out!</text>
   <text id="str_win_label_sell">Sell</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc13_descr_3"> Catch Burbot: [amount] </text>
   <text id="str_catching_message1">IMPRESSIVE!</text>
   <text id="str_weight_big">Big weight</text>
   <text id="entity_inhibitor_base">	Decreases the number of points earned during the time left.	</text>
   <text id="str_quest_auto_task_text">Catch [type] [weight]</text>
   <text id="str_quest_33_text">Hi! A deep pocket is amassing a collection of live fish, offering good money for [quantity] [fish type]! If you are on the shore with a rod, just try your luck!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_shtrafbat_descr">Smart battalion fish knows no fatigue and understand the hardship of army life. But there's one thing they don't know - not every MRE is edible!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_polosat_som_descr">A popular type in Amazon, unique with one characteristic - they can emit loud and distinctive sounds by resonating their swimbladders. Have simple feeding needs, omnivorous.</text>
   <text id="quest_14_7_2">Catch some Carps in the Loch Ness!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_2">Lab Order</text>
   <text id="str_fish_roach">Roach are members of the carp family. They swim in shallow rivers, often hiding under the cover of outcrops, algae, and trees that hang down in the water. Dried or salted roach is a perfect snack!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_nubler">A series of simple rods for people who are tired of catching small fish. This fishing rod is designed for fish weighing up to 2 kg.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_shar">Globefish</text>
   <text id="quest_14_1_3">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="str_shop_info_type_rare">rare</text>
   <text id="quest_2_10">Goodbye, Honey Coast</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_specprimanka_descr">A special bait for large predators is like catnip for kittens! If you want to catch a record catfish, there is no better bait!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc5_descr_8">Catch [amount] Tenches at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_end_of_action">Hurry up! Sale will end in %d %s</text>
   <text id="str_sale_search">Search in sale</text>
   <text id="quest_1_6_2">Catch Tenches weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_policy_head7">Changing or Deleting Your Information</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_general">General</text>
   <text id="str_fish_mramor_bichok_descr">Tube nosed goby are a benthic coastal fish. Usually tube nosed goby lurk under stones, hide in vegetation or burrow in the sand. They usually do not undertake large migrations, just moving from coast to deeper areas in winter. Tube nosed goby feed on fish, shell-fish, crustaceans, worms, etc. Like many other fish they can bear large variances in water temperature and drastic weather changes.</text>
   <text id="quest_13_4_1">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="str_time_for_net"> Choose a time </text>
   <text id="str_udochka_middler100">Middler</text>
   <text id="quest_2_7">Dream Fish</text>
   <text id="str_shop_info_for_phytovourus">For %s phytovorous fish</text>
   <text id="quest_1_6_desc">The National Zoo has opened an underwater section. They'll appreciate our help!</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_mol_goroh">Ground peas</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_udochka">Army fishing rod</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc10_descr_6">Catch rare Takifugu Rubripes at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="victory_day_12_1">	Catch some Ribbonfish to run the parade!	</text>
   <text id="str_notif1">Prove to the local fishermen who rules the waters!</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_karty_descr">When fish don't bite and there is nothing to do, you may play cards caught in that very pond. But first, surely, you'll have to collect the whole pack. </text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc14_descr_1">Catch Bottler: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_10_9_desc">A laboratory studying Mirror Carps asks you to catch some living in different habitats!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_7_3">Catch some Baikal Sturgeons!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_4">Silver Spoonbaits</text>
   <text id="str_fish_korvina">Atlantic croaker</text>
   <text id="str_ok_sending_progress">Приглашаем друзей ...</text>
   <text id="quest_13_6_desc">A laboratory is conducting a research and asks you to catch some fish from different habitats!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_burbot">Burbot are large fish that feed on invertebrates and small fish. Burbot are night hunters, and are easiest to catch from dusk till dawn. They also like cold water and even spawn in the winter - around December-February. Burbot are relatively rare, shy and difficult to catch.</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_net4_descr"> You can put this net to a depth of 6 meters. This net with strong and elastic multifilament canvas is ideally suited for catching big and active fish. The cells of this net too big to catch small fish. </text>
   <text id="str_fish_opener">Headhole</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_cancel">Remove</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc14_descr_6">Catch Opener-fish: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_5_2_1">Catch some Carps: they make an amazing gift!</text>
   <text id="quest_15_3_3">Catch Bottlers weighing 6 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="str_location_buy_label">Unlock for %s</text>
   <text id="quest_8_7_2">Catch some Siberian Graylings!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_52_text">Today is a [fish type] day! The person who catches [total weight] [fish type] will win a special prize!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_snakehead">Snakeheads are predators wh live among vegetation areas of rivers and lakes. They stick to shallow water and like to hide among snags and algae. Snakeheads feed on small fish, frogs, and insect larvae. An interesting fact: the snakehead needs to breath air, otherwise they die, even in clear water.</text>
   <text id="quest_11_1_desc">Here we are! Just look, how bautiful this place is! Let's cast the line now!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_30_text">I've just bought a new fish tank, [fish type] is still missing from my collection. Catch [quantity]</text>
   <text id="str_quest_103_text">If only little tiddlers are biting - don't throw them away, give them to me! About [quantity] will be perfect!</text>
   <text id="str_shop_info_type_common">common</text>
   <text id="entity_silver_coin">	Increases the player's silver!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_crucian">Crucian are quite small fish who inhabit boggy lowland lakes and rivers. They feed on plants and small invertebrates. Crucian are extremely hardy fish - being dormant they survive tough winters by staying close to the bottom.</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_this_tournament_has_ended">This tournament has ended</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer7">Daily Spin&quot; is a lottery, where you can win huge treasures. One spin every day is free for all players. To open the &quot;Daily Spin&quot; window, click on the arrow button in the upper right corner of the screen and choose the 1st icon on the left (&quot;777&quot;) from the drop-down menu.
    </text>
   <text id="str_fb_request_text_gift">My present to you for unlocking locations</text>
   <text id="entity_inhibitor_combo">	Decreases the number of points earned for keeping the fish inside the circle.	</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_soldatiki">Toy soldiers</text>
   <text id="og_open_thousand_islands">Not everyone would be brave enough to go so far... But here we are – I can see thousands of islands and I’d like to visit each of them!</text>
   <text id="tut_1_1_1">	It tells you what you need to do: to catch one fish!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_vimba">Vimba prefer specific, deep places in summertime, and even more so in winter. Vimba schools moving upstream eventually gather in reservoirs. Catching these strong fish needs vast experience. The fish may be attached to the hook only by a thin membrane under the lip, so they can easliy slip off. A vimba often beats an angler by literally spinning around, insistently freeing themselves from the hook.</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_specprimanka">Special Lure</text>
   <text id="str_novice_notif0">Can you catch a fat pike?</text>
   <text id="str_comics3">&quot;I need your help!&quot;</text>
   <text id="str_weight_rare">Rare weight</text>
   <text id="new_year_14_3">	Catch snowy fish weighing 60 kg in total.	</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_goodfish">Goodfish</text>
   <text id="new_year_3">	Sending Greeting Cards!	</text>
   <text id="new_year_9_2">	Catch some Black-Backed Shads weighing 0.8 kg each!	</text>
   <text id="str_location_seversky_descr">Seversky Donets it is a truly amazing river, which is famous by wide variety of fish species. It's hard to find a more beautiful place for a truly Russian fishing!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_7_3">Catch some Chars weighing at least 0.7 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_goodfish_desc">This fishing rod opens completely new horizons for beginning fishermen. Light and comfortable, allows you to catch fish weighing up to 1,5 kg.</text>
   <text id="new_year_7_2">	Spend some silver on the gift for Uncle Joe!	</text>
   <text id="entity_accelerator_base_title">	Basic score up	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_nase_imp">Nase are typical river fish eating organic remains that have settled on the bottom and various small creatures that crawl on the stony or hard sandy riverbed. The best nutritional conditions are at a medium depth of 1.3-5.9 ft, where the riverbed is covered by an alga carpet. Nase are shoaling fish that inhabit rapidly flowing deep water, often located near bridges.</text>
   <text id="str_ok_message">Стань крутым рыбаком!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_usat_golec">Stone Loach</text>
   <text id="victory_day_3_1">	Use a baiting to divert fish from the civil war.	</text>
   <text id="str_shop_title" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Shop</text>
   <text id="quest_5_10_2">Catch some fish weighing a specific total.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc4_descr_1">Catch Red-eyes: [amount]</text>
   <text id="entity_accelerator_fish_title">	Fish speedup	</text>
   <text id="quest_10_9_3">Catch some Mirror Carps in the Mountain Lake!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_steamed_corn">If you are going to catch a carp or a silver crucian, take along some steamed corn; they'll snatch it with a particular eagerness!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_8_2">Catch some Breams weighing at least 1.05 kg.</text>
   <text id="quest_8_2_desc">The laboratory workers are cooking some fish soup and ask you to catch some fishes for them.</text>
   <text id="quest_14_8">New Places</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_rainbow_descr">Bright exotic spoon can carry along all types of tropical fish. Recommended for use in Amazon!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_8_1">Catch some Eels in the Mountain Lake!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_5_3">Catch some Amur Catfish weighing 9 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_8">Bersch Protection Fund</text>
   <text id="str_tutorial_comics_text10">	Each quest is a great chance to earn some money!	</text>
   <text id="quest_4_9_1">Catch some Basses on the Sunset Coast!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_tank">Tank fish</text>
   <text id="halloween_8_1"> Catch some Amur catfish! </text>
   <text id="entity_placebo">	Distracts the player's attention. Does not influence the gaming process	</text>
   <text id="quest_15_7_2">Catch a Pintfish weighing 4 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_policy_text0">Drimmi LLC. and its Affiliates (&quot;Drimmi&quot; or &quot;we&quot;) are dedicated to protecting the privacy rights of our online users (&quot;users&quot; or &quot;you&quot;). Affiliates shall mean subsidiaries, parent companies, joint ventures and other corporate entities under common ownership. This Online Privacy Policy (&quot;Privacy Policy&quot;) has been crafted to inform you as to the ways we collect, store, use, manage, and, in certain circumstances, share the information you provide in connection with any Drimmi game or application (&quot;Service&quot;). Please note that the scope of this Privacy Policy is limited to only information collected from Drimmi through use of the Service.          By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We may amend the Privacy Policy from time to time, and we encourage you to consult the Privacy Policy regularly for changes. </text>
   <text id="victory_day_4_2">	Catch a Signalfish weighing not less than 3 kg – we need the best!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_shuchka">Grass Pike</text>
   <text id="str_fish_plotva">Roach</text>
   <text id="quest_3_8_desc">So, this place is not so &quot;hidden&quot; as it seemed. They have their own Fishing championship here!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_zolot_karas">Gold Crucian</text>
   <text id="quest_3_6_3">Catch some Thornies!</text>
   <text id="str_settings_vibra">Vibra</text>
   <text id="halloween_5_desc"> Coho has a very bright color. But all this does not disturb him to terrorize the hearts of fishermen! </text>
   <text id="str_amulet_proposal_desc_1">+15% weight</text>
   <text id="str_fish_paiara">Payara</text>
   <text id="str_fish_sibir_plotva">Siberian Roach</text>
   <text id="str_btn_rodinout_wait" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="33">Wait</text>
   <text id="new_year_18">	Christmas is Saved!	</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_spining_garpun_descr">This spinning lure matches its deterrent name - it may help you to reel in a large fish! The spinning is made from flexible and durable plastic, while the convenient handle prevents slipping, even when your palms are very wet palms.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_verhovka">Upswimer</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc3_descr_1">Catch Silver Crucians: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_5_3">Lost Item</text>
   <text id="halloween_2_2"> Earn some quantity of silver! </text>
   <text id="str_fish_small_bream">Small bream are a type of river fish closely related to bream. They differ from the latter by their smaller size and the fact that they are not as flat. Small bream prefer deep backwaters full of food and oxygen.</text>
   <text id="str_quest_42_text">I've just read the fishermen's horoscope, it says if you catch [quantity] [fish type] weighing at least [weight], good luck will be with to you all year!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_morskoy_okun">Norway Haddock</text>
   <text id="quest_13_5_desc">The National Zoo asks you to catch some rare local fish!</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_karty">Playing cards</text>
   <text id="halloween_2_1"> Cast a few lines to earn silver! </text>
   <text id="quest_13_8_desc">Have you ever heard about Thousand Islands? It is our next destination!</text>
   <text id="str_new_level_your_level">You reached level %d!</text>
   <text id="str_soon">SOON</text>
   <text id="quest_2_4_2">Cast your line several times.</text>
   <text id="new_year_3_3">	Spend some silver on greeting cards!	</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_santa_descr">New unique collection absorbed all the joy of the holidays!</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_you_won_some_goodies">You won some goodies!</text>
   <text id="str_spin_spinning">Spinning...</text>
   <text id="str_settings_music">Music</text>
   <text id="str_terms_head4">Rules of Conduct/Usage</text>
   <text id="og_open_beer_lake">A living legend before my very eyes! It is impossible to explain the nature and the very existence this place, but I have to believe that I really am here!</text>
   <text id="str_too_low_money" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="36">Not enough gold drimmis</text>
   <text id="quest_9_4_3">Catch the creature's head!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_7">Lab</text>
   <text id="quest_1_3_2">Catch 3 roaches!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc11_descr_8">Catch a rare Catfish at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="new_year_10_3">	Catch some icy fish weighing 18 kg in total!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_dried_descr"> Has a very dried kind and it‘s often deceives predators </text>
   <text id="str_shop_tab_food" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Lures</text>
   <text id="new_year_7_desc">	Uncle Joe waits us in his house, let's prepare some gifts for him!	</text>
   <text id="quest_4_1_3">Catch a Royal Fish weighing at least 0.45 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_10_2">Catch fish weighing 18 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_6_1">Catch some Ruffs in the Moon Bay!</text>
   <text id="quest_12_8_1">Cast your line several last times on the Fir Coast!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_auto_title">Quest</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_vertuska_descr">This spinning silvery lure easily glides beneath the water, attracting the attention of predators such as grass pike, eel, and skygazers.</text>
   <text id="new_year_4_3">	Put some silver in the Christmas money box!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc10_descr_8">Catch Paraiba at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_6_1">Arrival</text>
   <text id="quest_8_9_2">Cast the line several times to see the advantages of the rod!</text>
   <text id="victory_day_6_2">	Catch a Guerrilla-Fish heavier than 3.4 kg.	</text>
   <text id="str_comics10">&quot;But I still can't make myself...&quot;</text>
   <text id="quest_3_9_3">Catch White Eye weighing a specific total.</text>
   <text id="victory_day_5_2">	Catch a Penal Battalion-Fish heavier than 3.8 kg.	</text>
   <text id="new_year_15_3">	Catch fish weighing 12 kg in total for a Christmas feast!	</text>
   <text id="quest_11_8_3">Catch fish weighing 8 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="quest_3_2_1">Catch some Eels!</text>
   <text id="str_medium">Middle</text>
   <text id="quest_6_3_1">Use the Live spoonbait!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_4_3">Catch several fish weighing 7 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer5">Fishing rods have different max catch weight they can pull out. E.g., to catch a fish weighing 5 kg, you can use a rod for 7 kg catch, but not the one for 4 kg catch.
    </text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_molusk_descr">Omnivorous fish are crazy about shellfish meat. And this lure looks exactly like a drifting mollusk without its shell.</text>
   <text id="str_sequence_completed">Sequence completed</text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_3">Made of Rock - Get all achievements on Rocky Bay</text>
   <text id="str_location_amazon_descr">Ripping tropical rivers and the allure of the hidden waterways of the Amazon won't leave any experts indifferent. All caught trophies are worthy displaying on your wall!</text>
   <text id="new_year_12_3">	Catch some elf-fish weighing 25 kg in total.	</text>
   <text id="str_quest_11_text">A prize has been announced if you catch a fish weighing more than [weight]. Our guys have been fishing already! Good luck!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_svyaz">	Signalfish	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc1_descr_5">Catch Ides: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_2_1_desc">It's time to try a new spot!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc13_descr_7"> Catch [amount] Pirate Perch at least [weight] </text>
   <text id="str_spining_tutorial_1">The most important thing when fishing with a spinning lure is to move the lure correctly. Hold the button to move the reel up, release the button to move the reel down. Try to keep the reel within the designated area. The longer the reel stays within the limits, the higher the chance of a bite.</text>
   <text id="quest_8_8_desc">We've just stumbled upon a secret Fishsing Club. In order to become a member, you just need to follow some simple rules!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_6_3">Catch some Atlantic Salmon!</text>
   <text id="str_exit_message">Are you sure you want to exit?</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc3_descr_3">Catch Cisco: [amount]</text>
   <text id="new_year_8_2">	Catch some Santa-fish!	</text>
   <text id="quest_10_3">Mirrors</text>
   <text id="str_ach_location">Location</text>
   <text id="new_year_5_1">	Catch some Blue Breams for a Christmas feast!	</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_nautilus_descr">This skillfully made spoon causes a wave of nostalgia among the oldest fish. Ideal for chefs preparing Paleozoic cuisine.</text>
   <text id="og_open_river_valley">The way up the river valley was finally passed. One of the locals kindly offered us a place to sleep. The view of these mountains strikes the imagination! In the morning, we will try our hand in the new location!</text>
   <text id="str_shop_tab_raznoe" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Stuff</text>
   <text id="quest_6_8">Looking after Nature!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_7_3">Catch some Ides on the Honey Coast!</text>
   <text id="quest_9_5_desc">Locals allege that one can not catch a Sturgeon in a lake. Well, we'll prove them that miracles happen!</text>
   <text id="entity_expirience_title">	Experience	</text>
   <text id="str_policy_text10">If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@drimmi.com or support@drimmi.com</text>
   <text id="quest_7_7_desc">The National Zoo asks you to catch some particular fishes!</text>
   <text id="new_year_7">	Welcome Guests	</text>
   <text id="str_shop_info_for_predatory">For %s predatory fish</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_super_middler5000">Super Bear</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc2_descr_2">Catch White-Eyes: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_8_10_desc">Every fisherman dreams of fishing in the mysterious Loch Ness and discovering the secret of its denizen. Let's go then!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_7_1">Catch some Carps on Thousand Islands!</text>
   <text id="str_location_beer_descr"> Most real beer lake. Although they are widely considered fiction, they can still be found in some remote parts of the world.</text>
   <text id="new_year_16">	Unexplained Fish	</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_net5"> Quality big net </text>
   <text id="quest_5_7_desc">A farmer boasted about his incredible catch before his friends, but he exaggerated a bit, and now he asks for help. Let's catch the necessary amount of fish!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_8_3">Catch some Ratan Gobies weighing at least 0.5 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_no_money">Not enough money.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc5_descr_2">Catch Stone Loaches: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_kolbaska">Cervelat-fish</text>
   <text id="quest_9_9_desc">A laboratory studying Pikes asks you to catch some living in different habitats!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_aroma_najivka">Flavored bait</text>
   <text id="quest_14_7_desc">A laboratory is conducting a research and asks you to catch some fish from different habitats!</text>
   <text id="str_location_baikal">Sand Bank</text>
   <text id="str_rod_letter">R</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc10_descr_0">Catch Dorados: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_zefir_descr">	It was noticed, that Christmas fish bited especially well on a simple marshmallow.	</text>
   <text id="str_fb_text1">Wow! I have caught this [fish type] just now!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_krasnoperka">Red-eye</text>
   <text id="victory_day_11_2">	Catch some power-mad Fish Generals!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc9_descr_7">Catch [amount] Burbots at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="victory_day_7_1">	Catch some Bayonet-Fish	</text>
   <text id="str_atlas_record1">Record %2.3f%s</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_artelerist">Cannoneer</text>
   <text id="str_worldmap_mascot_tutorial">Choose, where we'll go for fishing!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_6_1">Catch some Barbels!</text>
   <text id="str_atlas_record2">on %s</text>
   <text id="str_fish_cask">BarrelBun</text>
   <text id="entity_inhibitor_fish_title">	Fish slowdown	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_omul">Omul</text>
   <text id="entity_inhibitor_base_score">	Basic points decrease twice slower for some time.	</text>
   <text id="new_year_15">	Presents for Children	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_dace">Dace have bluish-gray back, white belly silvery and yellowish fins. It’s body is moderately elongate and slightly compressed laterally. Dace, as a rule, can be found in small rivers clean and fast, but also in  flowing lakes and flood waters.  Dace prefers areas with hard sand or rocky bottom. Feeds on small invertebrates </text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_third_prize">3 sleepy fishes</text>
   <text id="str_fish_gorchak">Bitterling</text>
   <text id="str_inv_wearin">Use it</text>
   <text id="quest_11_5_desc">The National Zoo asks you to catch some rare local fish!</text>
   <text id="str_no_rod" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="36">Please choose rod.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_sosiska_descr">Belongs to the Beer-Vodka species, a member of the Oktoberfest family, mainly inhabits the drainage systems of brewery works. Fine with lager beer! </text>
   <text id="quest_1_2_3">	Earn some silver: sometimes nets can bring you some underwater treasure!	</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer13">You can find detailed information about a fish by clicking its image on the Trophies window or in the Location Viewer.
    </text>
   <text id="quest_12_3_desc">Local fishermen have started a Fishing championship and want us to join the competition!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_1_3">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_7_2">Catch some Mirror Carps weighing at least 1.2 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_chosen">The item is chosen</text>
   <text id="quest_7_1">Beautiful Valley</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_krovosos">Bloodsucker</text>
   <text id="quest_12_6_1">Catch some Grass Carps!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_8_1">Catch the most Arctic Chars.</text>
   <text id="quest_11_8_1">Catch some Redtail Catfish!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_6">Fighting Fish</text>
   <text id="str_fish_nalim">Burbot</text>
   <text id="str_terms_text2">You agree that you are willingly publishing the content on the Service using technology and tools provided by Drimmi LLC. You understand and agree that you may not distribute, sell, transfer or license this content and/or application in any manner, in any country, or on any social network or other medium without the explicit written permission of Drimmi LLC. You grant Drimmi LLC the right to act as an agent on your behalf as operator of the application.                  Any data, text, graphics, photographs and their selection and arrangement, (hereinafter &quot;User Content&quot;) uploaded to the Service are subject, whether in whole or in part, to unlimited commercial, non-commercial and/or promotional use by Drimmi LLC. Text, graphics, and photographs are uploaded by you and are the sole responsibility of the person from whom the User Content originated. Thus, users are responsible, and Drimmi LLC is not responsible for any files users upload, post, or otherwise make available. Drimmi LLC may or may not regulate User Content and does not guarantee the accuracy, quality, or integrity of any User Content posted via the Drimmi LLC application. By using Drimmi LLC you acknowledge and accept that you may be exposed to material you find offensive or objectionable. You agree that Drimmi LLC will not under any circumstances be liable for any User Content, including, but not limited to, errors in any User Content, or any loss or damage incurred by use of the User Content.                  Drimmi LLC reserves the right to remove and permanently delete any User Content from the Service with or without notice. </text>
   <text id="quest_1_1">Preparation first!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_10_text">The Biggest Fish Contest has started! It doesn’t matter what kind, only the weight, it must be more than [weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_1_6_4">Use the Spark rod.</text>
   <text id="quest_14_2_2">Catch an Arctic Grayling weighing 1.1 kg!</text>
   <text id="halloween_4_desc"> Rotan is so similar to an ordinary fish, but there is definitely frightening in it! </text>
   <text id="quest_13_5_2">Catch an Lampern weighing 0.23 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_paku_descr">Despite their resemblance to piranhas, they hardly eat any meat. Their inherent rations - nuts. Pacus grow fast and live long - up to 28 years. Real long-livers among Amazon fauna!</text>
   <text id="str_candy">Candy box</text>
   <text id="quest_11_2_1">Catch some Dorado!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_4_2">Catch some Vimbas!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc7_descr_1">Catch Baikal Sturgeons: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_salat">Salad</text>
   <text id="str_fish_shipovka_descr">Chipper is a small river fish, the largest specimens of chipper are rarely longer than 10 cm. And females are larger than males. This fish color is mottled but not bright, the basic tone is gray, light yellow or brown, on which are scattered small dark spots. It lives exclusively in clean waters. Chipper eats small invertebrates. Chipper prefers sandy-clayey soil, in which it can easily hide itself.</text>
   <text id="quest_13_6">Research</text>
   <text id="quest_5_1_1">Catch some fish.</text>
   <text id="str_daily_bonus_title">Daily bonus</text>
   <text id="victory_day_1_3">	Make several casts with your fishing rod.	</text>
   <text id="str_inv_wearoff">Take off</text>
   <text id="quest_8_7_1">Catch some Baikal Ciscos!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_7">Lab</text>
   <text id="quest_12_7_2">Catch some Blue Breams in the Mountain Lake!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc12_descr_7">Catch [amount] Common Carps at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_energy3">Strong tonic</text>
   <text id="str_policy_text4">A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk, generally to quickly identify a user's computer and to &quot;remember&quot; things about the user's visit, such as your preferences or a user name and password. The Service sends cookies to your computer when you access or view content of a Drimmi game. Information contained in a cookie may be linked to your personal information for purposes such as improving the quality of our service, tailoring recommendations to your interests, and making the Service easier to use. You can disable cookies at any time, although you may not be able to access or use features of the Service. </text>
   <text id="entity_inhibitor_base_title">	Basic score down	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_sky_gazer_imp">Sky gazers are predatory fish that prefer to swim mainly in the mid waters. They can reach a length of 3.35 ft and weigh up to 20 lbs. Sky gazers feed on young crucians and ichs. Their diet includes insect larvae and dayflies during their mass swarming. The mouth of a sky gazer is directed upwards. After reaching 3 inch, sky gazers switch to eating fish that have a mainly oblong body shape.</text>
   <text id="og_level_up">Today, I happened to come on the shore of the lake itself. I was enjoying the welcoming breeze and the rustle of reeds... Suddenly, just for a second, it became perfectly quiet. I recalled all the hardships I had surmounted, and it became clear to me that IT MADE ME STRONGER.</text>
   <text id="quest_3_10_3">Catch the biggest Burbot weighing at least 1.4 kg before you leave!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_10">Amazon!</text>
   <text id="str_policy_head8">Security</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_vodorosli_descr">Pretty often we catch some algae instead of fish. These algae can be dried, for instance, or used in a little collection, or for house decoration. Some algae is even edible and very tasty.</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question10">What do I need the Trophies window for?
    </text>
   <text id="quest_4_7_1">Silver spent on purchases will go for aquarium maintenance.</text>
   <text id="quest_11_2_2">Catch some Dorado weighing 4.5 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_piraiba_descr">Giant fish whose strength can be measured with a shark or swordfish's power. Since they usually break fishing rods and reels, it makes them hard to catch. Paraibas are called man-eaters in Brazil. You'd better not ask why.</text>
   <text id="str_open_location">You need to open previous location first</text>
   <text id="str_fish_arktich_golec_descr">Arctic char has silver color, with dark blue back and its sides are covered with rather large light spots. Arctic char lives in the cold northern lakes and rivers. In its appearance and way of life it is very similar to trout. Feeds on small invertebrates and other fish fry.</text>
   <text id="entity_accelerator_combo_title">	Combo points up	</text>
   <text id="str_new_level_post_title">New Level</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_krovosos_descr">This lure drowsily slides in the water, imitating the movements of a sluggish satisfied leech. All basins contain numerous predatory fish that are greedy for fat leeches! </text>
   <text id="str_update_check">Checking update ...</text>
   <text id="quest_1_3_4">Catch fish weighing 1 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_koriagi_descr">Some wood pieces taken out of the water looking amazingly like animals. And after being carved, rubbed down and lacquered, they will look perfect on your fireplace shelf.</text>
   <text id="victory_day_2_1">	Catch some General-Fish to reveal their leader.	</text>
   <text id="quest_1_5">Legendary Ruff</text>
   <text id="str_pause_exit">Quit to menu</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_tell_your_friends">Tell your friends</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc6_descr_2">Catch Round Gobys: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_6_1_3">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_3_desc">There's been a delay in the food supply from the town, so the monastery's refectory will be glad to buy any fish that can be cooked!</text>
   <text id="str_collection_compl">Collection complete!</text>
   <text id="str_new_achievement">New Achievement</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_plastikovaya">Plastic Rod</text>
   <text id="str_fish_sinec">Blue Bream</text>
   <text id="str_amulet_proposal_name_0">Bronze Amulet</text>
   <text id="str_fish_mramor_bichok">Tube Nosed Goby</text>
   <text id="quest_8_10">Mysterious Lake</text>
   <text id="entity_random_title">Random bonus</text>
   <text id="quest_10_7_desc">They say, there was a war a long time agoвЂ¦ It caused a number of new fishes to appear!</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question19">How can I import my Facebook friends?
    </text>
   <text id="str_fish_santa_descr">This amazing fish appears in reservoirs in a few days before Christmas.</text>
   <text id="quest_2_4_1">Use the Heron spining rod.</text>
   <text id="str_shop_confirm_item">Purchase for %d %s</text>
   <text id="str_fish_partizan_descr">	Indispensable participant of submarine defense forces.	</text>
   <text id="str_location_wildwood_pool">A silent deep lake with the occasional ray of sunlight glittering on its surface and penetrating the thick plant growth. It's not easy to get here, but it's well worth the effort - it is wonderful to sit on a lush grassy bank among the reeds, gazing at the dark-mirrored waters and waiting for a bite.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_piraiba">Paraiba catfish</text>
   <text id="quest_3_1_1">Catch some Daces!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_bayonet_descr">	Fish, that became famous in submarine wars thanks to its swiftness and accuracy.	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_gustera">Flat Bream</text>
   <text id="str_fish_araya">Ocellate river stingray</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_my_fishes">My fishes </text>
   <text id="quest_12_2_2">Catch a Chum weighing 2 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_11_7_1">Catch some Tilapias!</text>
   <text id="str_alert_please_select_spoon">Please use spoon-bait with spinning.</text>
   <text id="quest_10_2">Little Fisherman</text>
   <text id="str_shop_inapp_confirm_button">Buy for </text>
   <text id="str_fish_ygor">Electric eel</text>
   <text id="str_location_nochnaya">Secret Backwater</text>
   <text id="str_energy2_descr">Adds energy and allows for catching fish 15 percent larger</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_gold_prize">%d GOLD</text>
   <text id="halloween_6_3"> Catch Humpback Salmon on the total weight 4 kg! </text>
   <text id="quest_13_5">National Zoo</text>
   <text id="str_fish_cask_descr">BarrelBun is well-known for his quiet behavior. It could easily be mistaken for a very ordinary barrel</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_zemnovodnie_descr">Toads, frogs, lizards, newts - all of them may casually take your bait. Don't be in a hurry to throw them away! You may create, for example, a little terrarium of your own.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_golovastik">Tadpole</text>
   <text id="quest_6_6_2">Catch some Ruffs on the Sunset Coast!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_spining_molnia_descr">You can catch everything with this spinning lure, the only thing you will need is dexterity and the strength of your upper arms! The spinning is made from a state-of-the-art material, and titanium rings carry a load of up to a few tons. This reel, with its thick fishing line, will never pop out of its fixture.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_jeltoshek">Yellowcheek</text>
   <text id="quest_5_4_3">Catch some Stone Loaches!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_som">Catfish</text>
   <text id="str_fish_trekolushka">3-spine stickleback</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc13_descr_0"> Catch Crucian: [amount] </text>
   <text id="new_year_9">	Dressed Herring	</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_mol_goroh_descr">Ground peas are used as a lure for catching very large and cautious fish, such as Amur carp.</text>
   <text id="quest_9_8_3">Catch Verkhovkas weighing 8 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer10">Your Trophies contain all types of fish you caught, listing their names and weight. To open the Trophies window, click on the arrow button in the upper right corner of the screen and choose the 4th icon on the left (a book) from the drop-down menu.
    </text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_yantar_descr">Take a closer look at the amber - you can clearly see fossilized expressions of fear and terror in the faces of the insects.</text>
   <text id="str_tutorial_comics_text1">	Hi! Ready to go fishing?	</text>
   <text id="victory_day_8_1">	Catch some Penal Battalion-Fish for the new squad.	</text>
   <text id="str_location_sand_barrier">A mysterious hazy lake surrounded by ancient rocks and weatherbeaten northern trees. A cool wind sweeps over the water, riverside rushes and dry grass rustel mysteriously. Not every fisherman will be adventurous enough to explore wilderness like this. But the bravest fishermen will be rewarded – there are amazing fish living in this lake that can be caught nowhere else in the world!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc6_descr_4">Catch Salmon: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_1_1_3">Spend 120 silver coins on shopping. To prepare for fishing some expenses are required. 	</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_net2_descr"> Nets with cells 27-32 mm are usually used to catch medium-sized fish. In general these nets are designed for medium-sized herbivorous and omnivorous fish and small predators. Sometimes bigger fish can be caught with this net if it reels its tail into the net. </text>
   <text id="quest_9_1_desc">They say, a mysterious creature lives in this lakeвЂ¦ Let's see if it can prevent us from fishing there!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_ryapushka">Vendace</text>
   <text id="halloween_6_desc"> Threatened look of this fish makes it a welcome guest in city's aquariums. Especially in the midst of Halloween! </text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_take_your_prize">Take your prize </text>
   <text id="str_quest_32_text">[fish type] always bite well here! Let's bet on who can catch [quantity] first!?</text>
   <text id="str_policy_text5">The Service may contain links to other websites. The fact that the Service links to a website or presents a banner ad or other type of advertisement does not mean that Drimmi endorses or authorizes that third party, nor is it a representation of our affiliation with that third party. Drimmi is in no way responsible for the privacy policies of these other websites to which you chose to access from the Service. Please be sure to read the privacy policies of those websites when exiting the Service. </text>
   <text id="entity_accelerator_base_score_title">	Score speedup	</text>
   <text id="quest_2_7_3">Catch some Ides weighing 3 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_15_1_2">Catch fish weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_rub_motil">Bloodworm</text>
   <text id="str_fish_sereb_karas">Silver Crucian</text>
   <text id="quest_3_6_desc">Uncle Joe will appreciate if we bring back some rare species from this area!</text>
   <text id="str_tutorial_comics_text3">	Let's wait for a bite…	</text>
   <text id="str_check_net0">Get your net ready and get fishing!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_8_3">Catch some Eels in the Hidden Creek!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_5_2">Catch a Legendary Ruff weighing at least 1 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_net2"> Strong net </text>
   <text id="str_udochka_newbie2000">Longlass 2000</text>
   <text id="halloween_5_3"> Catch cohos on the total weight 3.5 kg! </text>
   <text id="quest_15_7_3">Catch Pintfish weighing 6 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_9_1">Catch some Round Bullheads.</text>
   <text id="quest_2_3">Born to Win!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_2_2">Catch some Siberian Roaches.</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_sign_success">Success</text>
   <text id="str_notif0">Take your fishing rod and show everybody how to fish!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_5">Environmental Protection</text>
   <text id="entity_accelerator_progress">	Increases indication of the green catch scale.	</text>
   <text id="quest_9_2_3">Catch some Carps.</text>
   <text id="victory_day_3_2">	Catch some riotous fish to end the chaos on the river bottom.	</text>
   <text id="quest_13_7_2">Catch some Ides in the Moon Bay!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_6_1">Catch some Blue Breams!</text>
   <text id="new_year_14_1">	Catch a snowy fish weighing 10 kg!	</text>
   <text id="quest_8_3_1">Catch some Verkhovkas.</text>
   <text id="quest_9_4_desc">What was that? There is something shaped like a head under water. Fisherman's instincts demand you to catch it!</text>
   <text id="str_candy_descr">	A special lure for unusual fish! Designed especially for catching Christmas fish.	</text>
   <text id="str_quest_102_text">Roasted fish in a sour cream sauce is an excellent dish! Catch [quantity] tiddlers of any kind -  the smaller, the better!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_2_2">	Catch fish weighing 1.5 kg in total!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_paiara_descr">Notable for their fangs on the bottom jaw, which is why payaras are called vampire fish.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_krasn_som_descr">Appreciated by amateurs of large fish. Although amateurs of aquarium food also don't mind having one object in their tanks - these catfish can easily attract attention. Valued as food in spite of their dark-colored meat.</text>
   <text id="quest_7_10_1">Catch a Taimen weighing at least 20 kg: let it be our parting gift to the farmer!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_4">Find a Reel from an Army Rod</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc1_descr_7">Catch Pike on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_freshwater_eel">Freshwater eel have long patchy bodies and slippery fine scales. They are able to cover long distances, move overland along the grass wet with rain or dew and travel from one reservoir to another, therefore reaching flowing endorheic and closed lakes. Freshwater eel prefer slow flowing water, but may also be found in swiftly moving streams as well. They dwell in lower layers at various depths and at bottom ground in cavities. Freshwater eels hunt at night in shallow waters and eat insect larvae, shell-fish, frogs and small fish.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_iron_desc"> A cheaper equivalent of Leech spoon. An ordinary piece of metal plate adapted for fishing . </text>
   <text id="str_fish_verhovka_descr">Upswimer are small freshwater fish. They resemble small bleak but have a wider body and head and a short lateral line. Verkhovka's favorite places are slow flowing small rivers, lakes, bottomland oxbow reservoirs, artificial ponds as well as pits with sandy and silty bottoms. Although verkhovka are small, they are voracious and omnivorous.</text>
   <text id="str_empty">Empty</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_minutes">min</text>
   <text id="quest_7_10_3">You'll also need some Gold to pay for the journey!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_1_1">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_korvina_descr">Bottom-dwelling fish that like splashing in coastal waves and lagoons. Their high quality meat is used widely in regional cuisines. Croakers feed on shellfish.</text>
   <text id="new_year_4">	Forest River	</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_igrushki">Stuffed toys</text>
   <text id="og_open_mountain_lake">My foot slipped off the mountain trail, and a few moments later a scattering of rocks left multiple ripples on the lake’s surface. For a moment, my heart sank, but I was able to keep the balance. Awe and admiration were mingled in me... Only now I have realized how beautiful this place is.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_mollusk">Clam</text>
   <text id="str_comics13">...started and headed towards adventures!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_beastm">Beastmaster</text>
   <text id="quest_14_6">Local Championship</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc0_descr_9">Catch Grass Pike on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question18">Where can I get lures and baits?
    </text>
   <text id="str_fish_perch">Perch are predators: the diet of an adult perch is largelymade up of other freshwater fish. Their habitat includes rivers, lakes, ponds, reservoirs and even lightly-salted sea areas. Perch prefer to stick to plain water basins, though they can sometimes be caught in high mountain reservoirs.</text>
   <text id="str_athlas_unknown_fish">Unknown fish</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_avatar">AVATAR</text>
   <text id="str_quest_12_text">Oh boy, I remember that fish I caught way back when! I guess fish like that are extinct these days! Prove my wrong, catch something weighing at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_soldatova">Soldatov's catfish</text>
   <text id="str_fish_zhereh">Asp</text>
   <text id="new_year_13_2">	Catch some fish in the Mountain Lake!	</text>
   <text id="quest_9_7_3">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="og_quest_1_8">A huge creature rushed out of the water, its eyes gazing at me in the moonlight. Just a moment later, I was squeezing it firmly with both my hands. Punch-drunk with success and surge of adrenaline, I realized that I was holding my first night catch!</text>
   <text id="victory_day_9_2">	Catch a Gunner-Fish for a certain total weight.	</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_goroh_descr">Green Peas</text>
   <text id="str_sale">Sale!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_8_2">Catch some Tankfish weighing 4 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_new_level_post5">Fish tremble at the sound of my name! Just became one level stronger in Gone Fishing!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_7_desc">Some real Ides can be found there! Don't miss the opportunity to catch it!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_15"> Persistent fisherman - Get all achievements on Heady water </text>
   <text id="str_new_level_reward_title">Your reward is</text>
   <text id="og_quest_2_3">The crowd fell silent, and the judge declared the winner... When he called my name, I could scarcely believe my ears. Only at the moment of awarding I realized how many contenders had been left behind. My top ranking is widely recognized and indisputable. Only a few are capable of it!</text>
   <text id="quest_9_4_2">Cast your line several times</text>
   <text id="quest_10_7_1">Catch some Ribbonfish.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_jivec">Live Bait</text>
   <text id="quest_6_8_3">Silver spent on purchases will go to the Wildlife Fund!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_10_3">Silver spent on purchases will go to pay the road</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer12">You can toggle sound and music, and vibration mode as well. You can also choose between metric systems to measure weight: kilograms or pounds. Language settings allow you to choose between English, German and Russian. To open the Game Settings window, click on the arrow button in the upper right corner of the screen and choose the 6th icon on the left (a gear) from the drop-down menu.
    </text>
   <text id="quest_6_4">Break the Record!</text>
   <text id="str_score">Score</text>
   <text id="str_shop_tab_bank" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Bank</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc6_descr_1">Catch Black Backed: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_play_tournaments">Play tournaments</text>
   <text id="quest_5_1">Fishing Master</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer16">The Quest description contains a number of items you need to complete it. Click on the Quest icon in the left-hand part of the screen to read the description.
    </text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc14_descr_4">Catch [amount] Drytails at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="quest_1_6_3">Catch a Tench weighing more than 0.7 kg.</text>
   <text id="str_location_gornaya_rechka">River Valley</text>
   <text id="str_fish_sibir_harius">Siberian Grayling</text>
   <text id="quest_11_2_3">Catch fish weighing 5 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_snow">	Snowflakes	</text>
   <text id="quest_15_3_2">Catch a Bottler weighing 4 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_11_5">National Zoo</text>
   <text id="victory_day_5">	Assault force	</text>
   <text id="str_quest_begin_cap">BEGIN</text>
   <text id="str_policy_head0">Privacy Policy</text>
   <text id="str_policy_head1">Information Collected and Used </text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc8_descr_3">Catch Carps: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_dough">With dough you may catch something bigger, for instance a shiny bream!</text>
   <text id="halloween_4_1"> Catch some Rotans! </text>
   <text id="str_fish_bersh_descr_imp">Volga zander are common zander relatives differing from them by the following: smaller sizes, absence of canine teeth on the mandible and the pre-operculum is fully covered by scale. Volga zander are generally freshwater fish residing in lower reach of rivers. Their basic food is carp and perch fingerling. Volga zanders longer than 0.5ft feed on solely fish. Due to the lack of canine teeth they are unable to snatch and swallow large prey (because of narrow their throat).</text>
   <text id="quest_6_7_desc">Locals will be grateful if we provide a fish supply for them to survive through winter.</text>
   <text id="quest_3_3_desc">A local zoo asked to bring back some species from our expedition.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_elf">Elf-fish</text>
   <text id="quest_12_2">Forester's Welcome</text>
   <text id="str_terms_head6">Disclaimer of Warranty; Limitation of Liability</text>
   <text id="quest_5_6_desc">Uncle Joe urgently needs fish for his café, and nobody can help him but us!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_3_1">Catch the biggest Silver Bream weighing at least 0.25 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_sale">SALE</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_krahmal">Starch</text>
   <text id="quest_15_7">Pintfish</text>
   <text id="str_catching_message0">GOOD!</text>
   <text id="str_location_thousand_descr"> There is a place in the United States which is ideal for the fans of fresh air and fishing. The peace and tranquility will help you relax after a tired fisherman busy day. Plunge into the cool expanse of Thousand Islands! </text>
   <text id="str_ok_all_friends_already_ingame">Все ваши друзья уже играют в Рыбное место на IOS</text>
   <text id="quest_5_5_desc">Wow, I can see a Goldfish there! Let's catch it, maybe it grants wishes!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc5_descr_4">Catch Catfishes: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_9_8_desc">The National Zoo asks you to catch some rare local fish!</text>
   <text id="og_complete_collection">The water surface was absolutely calm and impenetrable to my eyes. What lied beneath remained an enigma, and there were no signs of such an incredible luck coming. It was enough to take a quick look at the catch to understand that the Legendary Collection was assembled! Assembled by me!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_trubka"> Tube </text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc13_descr_5"> Catch American Catfish on total weight [summ weight] </text>
   <text id="quest_10_6_3">Catch fish weighing 4 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_1_desc">Is that really the place Uncle told us so much about? There's only one way to find it out!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_clam">Do you like salmon and sturgeon? Then always take some clams for bait. By the way, sea fishing without clams is not a good idea.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_bayonet">	Bayonet-Fish	</text>
   <text id="quest_2_10_2">Catch some Basses faster that the fisherman!</text>
   <text id="str_weight_record">New record</text>
   <text id="quest_11_4">Rare Leaf</text>
   <text id="str_fish_goldfish">Gold Fish</text>
   <text id="quest_4_3_1">Cast your line several times.</text>
   <text id="quest_15_3_1">Catch some Bottlers!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_4_3">Catch Marbled Sculpins weighing a specific total.</text>
   <text id="str_location_army">Victory River</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc0_descr_4">Catch Ruff: [amount]</text>
   <text id="new_year_12_1">	Catch an elf-fish weighing 6.2 kg!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_oscar_descr">One of the largest exotic fish with staggering coloring having numerous colorful variations. Their favorite food - insects.</text>
   <text id="quest_2_4">Find Winnie!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_middler15">Nubler</text>
   <text id="str_fish_amur_sazan_descr">Amur carp have long been considered delicious. They are seen as valuable in many countries: for instance, in the East, Amur carp were a kind of standard measure for the value of things, and the addressing a person as &quot;Carp&quot; meant a compliment, similar to 'Dear' today. Amur carp are very spectacular fish and possess a number of merits such as stamina, adaptability, caution, a strong sense of smell, hearing, vision, &quot;intelligence&quot; and &quot;wisdom&quot; in their own way; they are worth  close attention by fishermen.</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer9">The Location Viewer will show you the whole assortment of fish you can catch in each location.
        To open the Location Viewer window, click on the arrow button in the upper right corner of the screen and choose the 3rd icon on the left (a map) from the drop-down menu.
    </text>
   <text id="quest_10_1">Test Casting</text>
   <text id="halloween_1_2"> Catch a hell-fish at least 0.35 kg! </text>
   <text id="str_fish_osman_descr">Osman may be found in fast-moving river sources, both cold and warm springs, warm water and cold water lakes. In the summer osman reside in lakes and may be found everywhere from shallow waters down to 40m on stony or muddy ground among stonewort tousle. Young osman feed mainly on the larvae of midges and other insects. Osman bowels and caviar are toxic.</text>
   <text id="quest_2_7_1">Catch an Ide weighing at least 1.2 kg</text>
   <text id="str_fish_bystryanka">Spirlin</text>
   <text id="quest_6_2_3">Catch some Burbots!</text>
   <text id="new_year_4_2">	Catch some fish weighing 0.3 kg each for a special dish!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc4_descr_4">Catch Lake Trout: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_14_1_1">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_3_desc">Schmindler, a fishmonger, asks you to catch several fishes from his list!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc9_descr_5">Catch Barb on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_new_level_post2">Better, faster, stronger - new level on Gone Fishing!</text>
   <text id="str_market_remind">Reminder me later</text>
   <text id="quest_9_8_2">Catch some Gudgeons!</text>
   <text id="str_fishlist_razdelitel_2">Fish dreams</text>
   <text id="quest_4_9_desc">The lab is conducting an urgent research and needs some Basses from different habitats!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_2_3">Catch some Eels weighing 3.5 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_9_9_1">Catch some Pikes in the Loch Ness!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_10_2">Silver spent on purchases will go to pay the road!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_8">Thousand Islands</text>
   <text id="str_terms_head1">Intellectual Property/Ownership</text>
   <text id="quest_8_9_3">Catch fish weighing 5 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc8_descr_7">Catch [amount] Huchens at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_bloodworm">One more widespread type of bait. Fish like ides, cisco and asps are attracted to it.</text>
   <text id="quest_6_9_3">Catch some Catfish weighing at least 2.4 kg!</text>
   <text id="entity_inhibitor_combo_title">	Combo points down	</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_oparish_descr">Baikal sturgeon bite very well in spots baited with maggots! However, this type of bait also allows you to catch other large omnivorous fish.</text>
   <text id="quest_6_2_2">Castch some Silver Breams!</text>
   <text id="str_novice_notif2">Grab the rod! Water reservoirs are simply swarming with fish.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_gudgeon">Gudgeon are quite small greenish-grey-brown-silver omnivorous fish. They feed on bottom dwellerss, shell-fish and the spawn of other fish. Gudgeon are often eaten by larger predatory fish.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_shemaya">Shemaya</text>
   <text id="quest_10_7">Unexpected Mutation</text>
   <text id="victory_day_8">	Strength in Unity!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_round_goby">Round goby are a benthic species preferring lightly-salted coastal areas of seas with a depth of 3-5 meters, but they also inhabit rivers, reservoirs and lakes. They are notable for their immensely broad range of adaptation abilities. Round goby can survive in areas of low oxygen and possess the advanced ability to respire through their skin. They prefer solid stony ground but may be found on shell, sand or even muddy ground. They can obtain nutrition from a wide reange of sources, but their basic food is shell-fish, crustaceans and water plants. </text>
   <text id="str_udochka_middlerpro">Sp. Middler PRO</text>
   <text id="str_shop_info_max_weight">Max weight %.2f%s</text>
   <text id="quest_14_4_3">Silver spent on purchases will be used for making spoonbaits!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_tank_descr">Being under the harsh gaze of this fish one feels like an amateur! Be careful, it may burn.</text>
   <text id="str_spin_free_time">Free spin in %02d:%02d:%02d</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_elite2000">Sp. Elite 2000</text>
   <text id="quest_13_7_desc">A laboratory is conducting a research and asks you to catch some fish from different habitats!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_coho">Coho have a thick head, wide forehead, and a very short and deep caudal peduncle. These features help to distinguish them from humpback salmon, chum, red salmon, spring salmon and masu salmon. In seas and during visits to rivers coho have silver shining scales. They have delicious red meat that contains vitamins, microelements and minerals important for humans. Their meat is almost free from small bones and ideal for children.</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question9">What do I need the Location Viewer window for?
    </text>
   <text id="str_actions_time">This sale will end in %02d:%02d:%02d</text>
   <text id="str_unlocked_location">Location unlocked: </text>
   <text id="str_location_beer"> Heady water </text>
   <text id="quest_7_5_2">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc6_descr_6">Catch Trout on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_quest_36_text">I've been eating nothing but freshly cooked [fish type] for ages. If it's not a problem, please bring me [quantity] after you’ve finished fishing.</text>
   <text id="quest_6_2_1">Catch some Chubs!</text>
   <text id="victory_day_10_desc">	The meaning of this this war is more and more doubtable, but the river general asks again to get for him even more destructive power – the mighty Tank-Fish!	</text>
   <text id="victory_day_4_desc">	Released river general came back soon. He said that for the victory of his army troops urgently needs Signalfish!	</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_fb_title">Facebook</text>
   <text id="str_fish_danube_salmon_descr">A large species in the salmon family. Prefers the shady parts of reservoirs and various 'caches'. These hidden places are also their best hunting grounds for small fish. The minnows and gudgeons don't like that much!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_paku">Red-bellied pacu</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer19">НRight now you can't import your Facebook friends, as the feature is still under development. However, you can share your catch with your friends by posting its image on your wall. In order to do that, open the Selling window, make sure the &quot;Facebook&quot; box is checked and then click on the &quot;Sell&quot; button and authorize the application for the needed actions when asked.
    </text>
   <text id="quest_7_7">National Zoo</text>
   <text id="str_location_snow">Snow Shore</text>
   <text id="quest_3_9">Spoon-bait Test</text>
   <text id="quest_13_4_desc">Locals need silver to make new bells!</text>
   <text id="str_amulet_most_popular">POPULAR</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_middler50">Nubler H</text>
   <text id="str_fish_silver_crucian">Silver crucians are close relatives of gold crucians, but have several differences including body shape, color and habits. The body of a silver crucian is not as long as that of a gold crucian, their silver sides sometimes have blackish touches and bronze tints. Silver crucians are very mobile, and inhabit both stagnant waters and slow flowing rivers.</text>
   <text id="quest_3_5_3">Buy some Starch lures</text>
   <text id="str_location_GO">GO</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_title_wait">Wait</text>
   <text id="quest_10_3_desc">A local mirror-making plant needs pure silver to produce better mirrors. We can be of help!</text>
   <text id="str_novice_notif1">Catch the moment! Spawning season has begun in Gone Fishing!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_4">Fish Dish</text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_4">King of Mount - Get all achievements on Mountain Lake</text>
   <text id="victory_day_1_desc">	Sixth sense tells us that this place looks nothing like the ones where you fished before… There is only one way to make it clear – to throw the bait!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_opener_descr">Members of this species have a strong bony growths in the form of openers. Incredibly useful for outdoor activities!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_8">Tankfish</text>
   <text id="quest_1_5_1">Catch some Ruffs.</text>
   <text id="str_shop_gold_most_pop1">MOST</text>
   <text id="quest_7_2_3">Catch several River Trout!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_1_3">Catch some fish weighing at least 0.35 kg!</text>
   <text id="entity_random">Gives one of the bonuses randomly!</text>
   <text id="quest_12_3_1">Catch an Amur Catfish weighing 3 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_6_1">Catch some fish and exchange it for silver!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_completed_post_text">Hurray! One more quest completed! And now I'm moving forward to face new adventures!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc11_descr_0">Catch Chinese Perches: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_5_5">Goldfish</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_staff_descr">	A festive bait, designed for catching Christmas fish.	</text>
   <text id="quest_15_1_3">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="entity_inhibitor_base_score_title">	Score slowdown	</text>
   <text id="new_year_3_1">	Catch some fish and sell them to earn money!	</text>
   <text id="str_location_elovii">Fir shore</text>
   <text id="str_quest_105_text">It's our friend's birthday! Let's give him a mounted fish? I guess a huge [fish type] would be perfect! Will you catch it?</text>
   <text id="og_open_sunset_shore">Cliffs at sunset – what an unforgettable sight! The sun gets lost in the sunset haze, staining the waters of the Rocky Bay in fancy colors. At such moments, you can even forget about your fishing rod!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_spark">Spark</text>
   <text id="quest_11_9_3">You'll also need some Gold to pay for the journey!</text>
   <text id="new_year_6">	Snow Fields	</text>
   <text id="victory_day_12">	Victory parade	</text>
   <text id="quest_13_3_3">Catch fish weighing 4 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="quest_8_3_3">Catch some Baikal Pollans.</text>
   <text id="quest_8_4_desc">A local cafe needs much fish, the bigger — the better!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_6_2">Earn some silver!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_salmon_imp">Salmon or so-called salmo salar are one of the most famous, spectacular and tasty species of the salmon family. These surprisingly big fish can reach up to 50 ft long and weigh as much as 86 lbs. Their regular diet usually includes such small creatures as crustaceans and other small-sized ocean fish.</text>
   <text id="quest_5_10_desc">Local fisherment constantly talk about some Moon Bay... I think, I know our next destination!</text>
   <text id="quest_15_5_3">Catch Drytails weighing 6 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_4_1">Use the Army rod.</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer6">Depending on the time of day, different fish become active. You can get completely different catch when fishing in the same location at day and at night!
    </text>
   <text id="quest_15_5_desc">Our brewer friend promised to pay handsomely for a catch of Drytails -- they are good with his products!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_5_2">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_2_1">	Place a net to see the advantages!	</text>
   <text id="quest_9_2_1">Catch some Breams.</text>
   <text id="quest_14_4_2">Earn some silver!</text>
   <text id="tut_1_1_desc">	Hi! The main description of your quest is shown here.	</text>
   <text id="quest_3_2_2">Catch some Eels weighing at least 0.8 kg!</text>
   <text id="new_year_17_2">	Catch some Snowy fish!	</text>
   <text id="quest_2_4_3">Catch Winnie!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_8_3">Catch fish weighing 4 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_10">Sand Ridge</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_kukuruza_descr">Tiddlers are easily lured with corn and then eaten by predatory fish such as perch, sleepers, and grass pike.</text>
   <text id="str_finish_quests">Complete all quests on current location to open.</text>
   <text id="str_30th_close">Don't reset</text>
   <text id="str_terms_text1">All materials that are part of the Service (including, but not limited to, designs, text, graphics, pictures, video, information, applications, software, music, sound and other files, and their selection and arrangement) are protected by law from unauthorized use. The entire contents of the Service are copyrighted under the Moscow copyright laws and/or similar laws of other jurisdictions.                  You agree that no materials that are part of the Service may be modified, copied, distributed, framed, reproduced, republished, downloaded, scraped, displayed, posted, transmitted, or sold in any form or by any means, in whole or in part, or otherwise exploited without Drimmi's express prior written permission, except that the foregoing does not apply to your own User Content (as defined below) that you legally post on the Site. All other uses of copyrighted material, including any derivative use, require express prior written permission from Drimmi LLC. Any reproduction or redistribution of materials not in accordance with these Terms is expressly prohibited and may result in severe civil and criminal penalties.                  Drimmi LLC and/or its licensors remain the owners of right, title, and interest, including copyrights and other intellectual property rights, in and to all materials posted on the Services by Drimmi LLC. You acknowledge that you do not acquire any ownership rights by using the Service or by accessing any materials posted on the Service by Drimmi LLC, or any derivative works thereof.                  Drimmi LLC grants you a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable, limited scope license to use the Service solely for the purpose of viewing and using the applicable Services and for no other purpose whatsoever. Your license to use the Services is limited by these Terms. </text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_morozko_descr">This fish wakes up only in the winter and hibernates in the summer. It bites well when fishing under the ice (as Chilly Willy will confirm). According to legend, this fish substitutes the Magic Goldfish at the Christmas Holidays, because the latter is drunk like a fish during this period.</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question2">How can I start fishing?
    </text>
   <text id="str_new_level_post3">No limits to perfection - got new level on Gone Fishing!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_9">Zoo Order</text>
   <text id="quest_7_9_desc">The National Zoo officials insist that there is one more fish species they need!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_3_desc">There is a legend saying that only the luckiest fishermen can catch an American Catfish hereвЂ¦ Fancy to check it out?</text>
   <text id="victory_day_7">	Bayonet charge	</text>
   <text id="quest_15_2_desc">The brewer accidentally dropped a collection beer bottle into the lake. He's going to fork out if someone could return it back.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_gold_crucian_imp">Gold or yellow crucians are longstanding inhabitants of ponds, stagnant water lakes, oxbows and even small swamps. A gold crucian has a long, almost round body, red-copper sides and dark-red fins. Gold crucianscan reach 1.6 ft in length and up to 11 lbs in weight. In overpopulated reservoirs they become tiny - little larger than small coins. Gold crucians are known for their toughness and  ability to live in habitats with little oxygen in the water.</text>
   <text id="str_location_ask_button">Ask friends</text>
   <text id="quest_6_8_1">Earn some silver!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_7_desc">Uncle Joe has lost his lucky card that he kept for years. We must find it at all costs!</text>
   <text id="quest_12_7_1">Catch some Blue Breams on the Fir Coast!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc3_descr_5">Catch Whitefin Gudgeon : [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_6_8_2">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_begin">Begin</text>
   <text id="str_amulet_left">%d REM.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_sudak">Zander</text>
   <text id="quest_11_9_2">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total! You'll need something to eat during the journey!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_whitefin_gudgeon">Whitefin gudgeon are a very rarespecies and little is known about them. Unlike common gudgeon, whitefin gudgeon adults have long barbells, which reach their rear eye edge and have an unusual color. They are only rarely found in small rivers and in the upper course of medium rivers and have never been observed in ponds and lakes.</text>
   <text id="quest_5_3_1">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_1">Are We There?</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc7_descr_8">Catch Baikal Sturgeon at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="str_shop_gold_most_pop2">POPULAR</text>
   <text id="new_year_18_3">	Catch fish weighing 35 kg in total faster than others!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc2_descr_1">Catch Daces: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_spining_garpun">Sp. &quot;Harpoon</text>
   <text id="str_fish_zmeegolov">Snakehead</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc0_descr_1">Catch Roach: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_13_6_3">Catch some Royal Fish on the Sunset Coast!</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_worm_descr">A worm is the most popular bait for catching some types of fish. Large gudgeon, ruff, ide and tench are attracted to spots baited with worms!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc3_descr_9">Catch Salmon at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="str_exit_yes">Yes</text>
   <text id="quest_7_6_2">Catch several Shads weighing at least 0.9 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_collection_new">New collection item</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc4_descr_6">Catch Mirror Carp on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_trekolushka_descr">Stickleback are agile, schooling fish, living in both freshwater and seawater. Unfortunately, the fish has no commercial value and is used as poultry feed.</text>
   <text id="new_year_9_1">	Catch some Black-backed Shads!	</text>
   <text id="str_catching_message3">WONDERFUL!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_2_3">Catch Gudgeons weighing a specific total.</text>
   <text id="str_alert_spoon_crashed">Your spoon-bait is crashed.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_rechnaya_forel">Trout</text>
   <text id="quest_1_3_5">Use Dough bait!</text>
   <text id="str_location_honey_shure">Honey Shore is famous not just for its wonderful nature and amazing sunsets, but also for its abundance of its fish. So the fishing is perfect here. But because of that there are also a lot of other anglers around!</text>
   <text id="str_comics14">A familiar outline!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_7_desc">The National Zoo needs our help with their famous great aquariums!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_4_desc">The Fisherman's Guide says that there are Marbled Sculpins in this area! Can we catch some, I wonder?</text>
   <text id="str_fish_omul_descr">Omul feed on large crustaceans, young goby, cisco fries, smelt and Arctic cod in seas. When they are in areas with high plankton density, omul switch to eating planktonic crustaceans. Omul are oily fish. Large oil stores help them to survive severe winter conditions. .</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_live_bait">If you have ever heard a story about a 300-kilogram catfish caught by a master fisherman,you can  be sure that the guy was fishing with exactly this kind of cheap live bait!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_interface_requirements">Requirements:</text>
   <text id="quest_12_4">Open Air Rest</text>
   <text id="quest_3_5_1">Buy some Live Bait sponbaits</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc14_descr_8">Catch JoyPint on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_15_1_desc">How did you find us? Well, you're here, then catch some fish for dinner and join us at the table!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_2">Elusive Eel</text>
   <text id="str_tutorial_comics_text_skip">	Skip the tutorial	</text>
   <text id="quest_14_8_2">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total! You'll need something to eat during the journey!</text>
   <text id="new_year_8_3">	Catch some Santa-fish weighing 15 kg in total!	</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_rachok_descr">To fish, this lure looks exactly like an edible crustacean hurrying about its business. No self-respecting omnivorous fish will ever miss such a penny from heaven! </text>
   <text id="quest_14_8_1">Cast your line several last times on Thousand Islands!</text>
   <text id="str_buy_uncatched_fish">Pull</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc10_descr_4">Catch Oscar on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_rod_letter_desc">Use with fishing rod</text>
   <text id="str_fish_siberian_roach">Siberian roach are quite small fish that differ from common roach by their unusual color. They avoid cold and swift water or muddy ground, preferring clear and deep areas with still, warm water and a sandy-muddy or stony or argillaceous bottom. Siberian roach may be found near sunken shrubs, snags, among water vegetation close to the shore.</text>
   <text id="victory_day_7_3">	Catch fish for a certain total weight .	</text>
   <text id="quest_4_5_2">Catch some Golden Crucians weighing at least 0.35 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_snow_descr">	A spoon-bait made of shiny metal snowflakes, especially useful for catching Christmas fish. 	</text>
   <text id="entity_expirience">	Increases the player's experience!	</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_strekoza">Dragonfly</text>
   <text id="quest_8_3_2">Catch some Sabrefish.</text>
   <text id="str_policy_text2">You understand and agree that we may be required to disclose any personal information if required to do so by law or in good faith believe that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to avoid liability, to comply with legal process, including but not limited to a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, or to protect our rights and property, or that of the public. Note that Drimmi is not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that Drimmi may receive.          Additionally, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, customer information may be transferred to Drimmi's successor or assignee, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law. </text>
   <text id="quest_15_2">Rare Bottle</text>
   <text id="str_fish_arktich_golec">Arctic Char</text>
   <text id="quest_1_8_desc">Some fish inhabiting this area can be caught only in the night... But we all know that darkness can not stop a real fisherman!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc11_descr_3">Catch Eels: [amount]</text>
   <text id="new_year_2_1">	Catch some fish — it will help you to concentrate and find the solution!	</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_rainbow">Ekzo</text>
   <text id="quest_14_2_1">Catch some Arctic Graylings!</text>
   <text id="quest_9_7">Spoonbait Test!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_4_2">Use the Middler PRO rod!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc8_descr_2">Catch Perches: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_9_5">Catch Me, If You Can</text>
   <text id="entity_accelerator_base">	Increases the number of points earned during the time left.	</text>
   <text id="str_atlas_weight">Weight: %.3f %s</text>
   <text id="str_spining_letter_desc">Use with sppings</text>
   <text id="halloween_7_desc"> This fish looks like a real evil incarnate. To catch it you need to have much courage! </text>
   <text id="str_fish_black_backed">Black-backed shed are large fish with a dark-violet or almost black back and dark fins with well-developed teeth. Black-backed shed are predators feeding on mainly small fish. They can live for about 6-7 years. In the spring from March to April they head northward, mostly along western coasts in midsea areas.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_snow_descr">These funny creatures can be noticed not far from Santa-fishes in holiday time.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_pirapytanga">Piraputanga</text>
   <text id="quest_8_6_3">Silver spent on purchases will go to make the figurine.</text>
   <text id="str_comics7">&quot;Please, come inside, I'll make you some tea!&quot;</text>
   <text id="str_fish_amer_som">American Catfish</text>
   <text id="str_fish_chehon">Sabre</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question13">Where can I find Fish details?
    </text>
   <text id="quest_7_2_2">Catch several Graylings weighing 2 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_jeltoshek_descr">A predator and the largest species in the cyprinoids family, named for the yellow-gold stains on its cheeks. The bigger a yellowcheek, the more colorful its cheeks. Yellowcheek's meat is very tasty, and real gourmets will surely appreciate this!</text>
   <text id="victory_day_7_2">	Catch a Bayonet-Fish heavier than 4.7 kg.	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_kolbaska_descr">Belongs to the Beer-Vodka species, a member of the Oktoberfest family, mainly inhabits the drainage systems of brewery works. Must be consumed only with dark &quot;Guinness&quot;, otherwise intoxication may occur! </text>
   <text id="new_year_15_2">	Catch some ball-fish to decorate the Christmas Tree!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_karp_descr">Carp are large yellow-green and brown omnivorous fish, they have thick longish body covered by coarse, smooth, gold-green-grey-brown scale. Carp may live for 50 years or more. The average carp weighs 9 kg, but it can reach 35 kg. Carp eat almost without breaks because they belong to the group  of stomachless fish. They are called &quot;omnivore water spirits&quot; and resemble pigs in their lack of discrimination regarding food choice, as well as their rapid growth and gluttony.</text>
   <text id="quest_6_1_desc">The Moon Bay. Here we are. Just look, how beautiful nature is!.. Quickly, take your rod!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc14_descr_0">Catch any fish on total weight: [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="victory_day_10_1">	Catch some Tank-Fish to raise a unit!	</text>
   <text id="quest_9_5_2">Catch a Sturgeon weighing 17 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_shop_inapp_confirm_text">Buy now %d gold</text>
   <text id="str_fish_lenta">Ribbon-shaped fish</text>
   <text id="quest_6_7_3">Catch some fish weighing at least 2 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_semga">Salmon</text>
   <text id="victory_day_3_3">	Catch fish for a certain total weight.	</text>
   <text id="quest_1_9">Preparing to Move Out</text>
   <text id="new_year_17_3">	Catch some Elf-fish!	</text>
   <text id="str_tired_fish_text">Fish is about to get away! Long struggle harassed it - continue, and it will be easier to catch it!</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer2">Click on the hook button in the lower right corner of the screen. After the line is cast, wait till the hook button starts blinking, then click it again, and a mini-game will start.
    </text>
   <text id="halloween_3_2"> Catch Thornies at least 0.12 kg! </text>
   <text id="str_fish_sabre">Sabre fish prefer large rivers free from algae along with reservoirs and big lakes. In the daytime they float at mid water level or near the surface, at nighttime they sink to significant depths. When frosts arrive sabre fish swim down into cavities and deep places. They feed on mainly insects and their larvae as well as worms and fingerling.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_morskoi_ugor">Conger Eel</text>
   <text id="quest_6_3_3">Catch fish weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_zefir">	Marshmallow	</text>
   <text id="quest_10_7_2">Catch some Ribbonfish weighing 4 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_army_rod">A portable fishing rod should easily fit inside a soldier's backpack! A hungry soldier can catch up to 15 kg of fish with it.</text>
   <text id="str_btn_rodinout_podsech" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="33">Hook</text>
   <text id="new_year_6_1">	Cast your line several times!	</text>
   <text id="str_quest_auto_task_text_any_fish">a fish</text>
   <text id="quest_10_4_desc">A fisherboy has lost a reel from his rod. Let's show him that a real fisherman can do without one!</text>
   <text id="str_night">Night</text>
   <text id="quest_8_1_desc">Just see how calm it is there! One can sit here fishing for hours!</text>
   <text id="str_too_early" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Too early !</text>
   <text id="quest_6_8_desc">We should help the Wildlife Fund to protect this beautiful place!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_testo">Dough</text>
   <text id="str_fish_partizan">	Guerrilla-Fish	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_lin">Tench</text>
   <text id="quest_12_8_desc">Let's go towards the Northern Donets! Are we ready to move out?</text>
   <text id="quest_2_9_desc">The National Park asks you to catch some Nases!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_goodfishs_desc">Goodfish brand represents good quality for a good price. This extraordinary rod provides balance and allows you to catch fish weighing up to 3,5 kg.</text>
   <text id="victory_day_11_3">	Catch the most dangerous Tank-Fish weighing not less than 5.2 kg!	</text>
   <text id="quest_11_7">Jungle Gold</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer8">Collections combine thematically similar objects. You can find collectibles by completing quests and unlocking new locations. When you complete a collection, you get a reward. To open the Collections window, click on the arrow button in the upper right corner of the screen and choose the 2nd icon on the left (a glowing casket) from the drop-down menu.
    </text>
   <text id="str_location_scores">This is your best result for this location.</text>
   <text id="quest_4_4">Marble Colour</text>
   <text id="str_location_army_descr">What can be better than the smell of gunpowder and the heat of a tank engine? The only answer is - fat, hostile fish! Take the challenge to test your stamina, endurance and strength.</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_staraya">Old Rod</text>
   <text id="str_fish_canal_som_descr">Channel Catfish widespreaded in central and southern states of the USA. Channel Catfish meat has excellent taste - it is the main object of pond production in the United States. </text>
   <text id="str_amulet_info_2">Golden Amulet: Gives 30% increase to the weight of the catch!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_trubka_desc"> A cheaper equivalent of a Spinner spoon . The elongated tube can confuse easily even the most cautious beasts of muddy bottom! </text>
   <text id="str_bank_awaiting_android">Connecting to Google Play</text>
   <text id="str_shop_amulet_buy_for">Buy for</text>
   <text id="str_fish_karas">Crucian</text>
   <text id="entity_gold_coin">	Increases the player's gold!	</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_prizes_title">Tournaments prizes</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_longx">Longlass X</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc9_descr_6">Catch [amount] Common Carps at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_location_snow_descr">Snow is all around! Strange but few species manage to survive even at such low temperatures!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_soldatova_descr">Large freshwater fish, its population is decreasing. No wonder - few other fish can display such huge size and weight. Basic diet: carp, pike, crucian and even birds!</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_fb_desc">To play tournaments we will need your Facebook name and avatar.</text>
   <text id="quest_9_2">Welcome Gift</text>
   <text id="str_fish_bottle"> Bottler </text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc1_descr_6">Catch Nase on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_15_5_2">Catch a Drytail weighing 2 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_tadpole">If you dream of catching a conger eel or a large zander, your backpack should always contain a dozen tadpoles for bait.</text>
   <text id="quest_11_3_1">Catch some Piranhas!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_2_1">Use the Nubler rod.</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_name_score">NAME/SCORE</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_devil_descr">The Hell-fish or Sea Devil lives near the sea bed and likes to scare timid divers and pearl divers. It tastes like a skunk’s tail, but once dried and blown up it is a perfect substitution for an everlasting Halloween pumpkin!</text>
   <text id="str_check_net2">You've caught lots of fish. Pull up your net!</text>
   <text id="og_catch_funny_fish">I could hardly believe my eyes, but the legendary being was in my hands! Scientists would say that anything like this doesn’t exist in nature. Some would say I was just lucky. But I know for sure that fortune smiles upon the best of us!</text>
   <text id="new_year_12_2">	Catch some elf-fish!	</text>
   <text id="entity_inhibitor_fish">	Slows down the motion of the fish for some time - it becomes easier to catch it.	</text>
   <text id="victory_day_12_2">	Catch a big Ribbonfish, which will be a star of the parade! It should be heavier than 2.4 kg!	</text>
   <text id="new_year_3_2">	Earn some silver!	</text>
   <text id="quest_5_4">Free Willie!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_7">National Zoo</text>
   <text id="str_terms_text3">The Service may include an opportunity to purchase virtual, in-game currency (&quot;Virtual Currency&quot;) that may require you to pay a fee using &quot;real money&quot; to obtain the Virtual Currency. The Service may also include virtual, in-game digital items (Virtual Goods) that may be purchased from Drimmi LLC for real money or for Virtual Currency. Virtual Currency and Virtual Goods can never be redeemed for real money, goods, or any other item of monetary value from Drimmi LLC or any other party. You understand that you have no right or title in Virtual Goods or Virtual Currency.                  Your purchase of Virtual Currency and/or Virtual Goods is final and is not refundable, exchangeable, transferable, except in Drimmi LLC's sole discretion. You may not purchase, sell, or exchange Virtual Currency or Virtual Goods outside the Service. Doing so is a violation of the Terms and may result in termination of your account with the Service and/or legal action.                  Drimmi LLC retains the right to modify, manage, control and/or eliminate Virtual Currency and/or Virtual Goods at its sole discretion. Prices and availability of Virtual Goods are subject to change without notice.</text>
   <text id="quest_6_5_desc">Let's contribute to the environmental protection and pull out an old rusty can from the water!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc2_descr_6">Catch Rotans on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_new_level_congrats">Congratulations!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_brand_rotan">Brand Rotan</text>
   <text id="quest_1_9_desc">It's time to look for new fishing spots! But first, we need to prepare for the journey.</text>
   <text id="quest_9_1_1">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="str_shop_tab_bait" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Baits</text>
   <text id="str_catching_message4">UNBELIEVABLE!</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_motil_descr">If you're not interested in tiddlers and want to catch only medium and large-sized fish, using chopped bloodworm is a must! Just throw a couple of handfuls into the water and cast the line!</text>
   <text id="str_policy_head3">OthersТ Information</text>
   <text id="new_year_4_1">	Catch some fish for a Christmas feast!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc7_descr_5">Catch Amur Catfish on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc0_descr_5">Catch Crucian: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_3_1_desc">Let's see if we can catch any fish inhabiting this hidden creek!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_taimen">Hucho perryi</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer20">You can get Gold as a reward for completing tasks, netting fish, playing the &quot;Daily Spin&quot; lottery or unlocking new locations. Also, any player can buy extra Gold from the Bank.
    </text>
   <text id="str_day_night_comment">Pay attention - you can catch some fish only in the afternoon, and the others only at night!</text>
   <text id="victory_day_5_1">	Catch some Penal Battalion-Fish	</text>
   <text id="str_market_text">Thank you for giving us a high rank! We hope you enjoy playing!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_10">Heading towards Adventures</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc13_descr_6"> Catch Channel Catfish on total weight [summ weight] </text>
   <text id="quest_14_5_2">Catch a Channel Catfish weighing 3 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_7_3">Catch some Nases on the Honey Coast!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_okun_descr">This lure perfectly imitates the movements of small fry. Small predators, like perch and sleepers, attack it promptly! </text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_net0"> Usual net </text>
   <text id="str_location_zakatnii_bereg">Rocky Bay</text>
   <text id="new_year_17">	Fancy Fish	</text>
   <text id="quest_8_2_1">Catch some Baikal Graylings.</text>
   <text id="halloween_7_3"> Catch arthrodiras on the total weight 140 kg! </text>
   <text id="og_defeat_friend">In the uphill struggle on the brink of human capabilities I was able to beat %Username%. The best man wins!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_9">Nase Hunt</text>
   <text id="str_terms_head">Terms of Service</text>
   <text id="quest_7_5">River Valley</text>
   <text id="str_atlas_number">Quantity: %d</text>
   <text id="quest_15_6">Openerfish</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc2_descr_7">Catch Arctic Char on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="victory_day_2">	River General	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_frogprince">Prince-frog</text>
   <text id="quest_1_4_1">Catch a necessary number of Small Breams.</text>
   <text id="victory_day_1_1">	Catch some inhabitants of the river and look at them closely	</text>
   <text id="str_shop_bought">Bought</text>
   <text id="quest_5_8_2">Catch some Eels on the Sunset Coast!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_9_3">Catch some Round Bullheads weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_ersh">Ruff</text>
   <text id="quest_15_7_1">Catch some Pintfish!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc6_descr_7">Catch Humpback Salmon on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_elitesmpl_desc">Elite family owes their staggering reputation to technical gimmicks. The spinning of real pros, favoring fish weighing 30 kg.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc14_descr_3">Catch BarrelBun: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_4_2_3">Catch fish weighing 3 kg in total 5 kg.</text>
   <text id="new_year_9_3">	Catch some Black-backed Shads weighing 8 kg in total!!	</text>
   <text id="str_quest_55_text">There is a lot of [fish type], especially this year!  We need to reduce the population to protect the other fish! Catch [total weight]!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_3_desc">There is an incredibly rare lizard living in this area! The National Zoo will pay handsomely for one of these!</text>
   <text id="str_comics9">&quot;I've been dreaming to fish in the most famous lakes!&quot;</text>
   <text id="str_fish_ayha">Chinese perch</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc3_descr_4">Catch Gold Crucians: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_plastic">A classic rod for rookie anglers. It is strengthened comparing to its simpler lookalike and allows you to catch larger fish. The fishing rod is designed for fish weighing up to 1.25 kg.</text>
   <text id="quest_14_4_1">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_43_text">They say that the older and the bigger a [fish type], the tastier it is. I want to try it! If you could catch a [fish type] weighing at least [weight], that would be great!</text>
   <text id="str_shop_tab_energy" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Energy</text>
   <text id="quest_8_4_1">Catch some Sabrefish weighing at least 0.5 kg.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_skalp"> Scalpel </text>
   <text id="quest_9_9_3">Catch some Pikes on the Honey Coast!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_iron"> A piece of iron </text>
   <text id="new_year_12_desc">	Christmas is coming, and it has an impact on local inhabitants — you can see an elf-fish in the water here and there!	</text>
   <text id="quest_11_2_desc">In order to convince natives to stay there on their territory, we have to make a gift for their shamanвЂ¦ a fish-gift!</text>
   <text id="str_settings_sounds">Sounds</text>
   <text id="quest_2_1">Shifting Towards Better</text>
   <text id="quest_4_2_2">Cast your line several times.</text>
   <text id="quest_6_1_2">Catch fish weighing 5 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc8_descr_4">Catch Zonders: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_9_6_3">Catch fish weighing 5 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_dogfish_descr">All fish from this family are poisonous, so be careful when catching them. Poison is located in fish skin and internal organs. Predatory and dangerous type.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_chernospinka">Black-backed</text>
   <text id="str_fish_pirania">Piranha</text>
   <text id="str_change_day_night_text">Change the time of the day a get access to the relevant fish!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc2_descr_3">Catch Barbs: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_12_1">Silence and Harmony</text>
   <text id="quest_6_1_1">Catch some fish.</text>
   <text id="quest_2_9_1">Catch a Nase weighing at least 0.7 kg.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_breadcrumb">A real fisherman always uses this bait and there's a neverending supply! But you'll only land a tiddler with this stuff!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_3_3">Catch Rotans weighing a specific total.</text>
   <text id="str_fishlist_razdelitel_1">Rare</text>
   <text id="str_comics12">Why not? Next morning, we have...</text>
   <text id="quest_12_5_2">Catch some Chinese Perches!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_5">Trout Catcher - Get all achievements on River Valley</text>
   <text id="quest_13_5_3">Catch some Lamperns weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_change_day_night_title">Day / Night</text>
   <text id="str_quest_44_text">Guests are going to be plump! But there's nothing to stand on. It would be great if you caught [quantity] [fish type]. But each fish shouldn't be under [weight]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_ozernaya_forel">Lake Trout</text>
   <text id="quest_10_9">Lab Order</text>
   <text id="quest_bonus_1_1">	Catch 2 fish!	</text>
   <text id="str_location_pinery_river">How nice it is to sit on the shore of a quiet river flowing among the pinery somewhere in the virgin forests, to cast the line and wait for a bite while enjoying the warm breeze, the babbling currents and the warbling songs of the woodland choir.</text>
   <text id="str_policy_text7">You may review, update, correct or delete any personal information by changing the applicable information in your profile page on Facebook and/or other social network(s). If you completely delete all this information, your account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your record in our system, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request if we are not legally obligated to retain the record. </text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_title_result">Your prize</text>
   <text id="str_exit_no">No</text>
   <text id="str_fish_sibir_harius_descr">Siberian grayling are the most widespread freshwater fish of the Northern Hemisphere. They can live in streams, rivers and large rivers (in mountains and tundras), oxbows, and also lakes of different types: from deep clear glacial lakes to small tundra lakes. As with other salmon, Siberian graylings are sensitive to water clarity and water oxygen concentration, which is why they are more frequently found in streams and foothill rivers, in cold lakes in the southern areas of their range.</text>
   <text id="new_year_13_3">	Cast your line several times in the Moon Bay.	</text>
   <text id="quest_11_6">Variety of Species</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc2_descr_0">Catch Brand Rotans: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_location_unlock_title">Unlock new fishingspot!</text>
   <text id="str_fb_text3">Look what I have caught!</text>
   <text id="new_year_2">	Stolen Christmas!	</text>
   <text id="str_amulet_proposal_name_2">Golden Amulet</text>
   <text id="str_spin_win_prizes">Win prizes</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_sign_success_desc">You have successfully signed up to this Tournament!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_8_3">Catch some Ciscos weighing 7 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_mulaj"> Dummy </text>
   <text id="str_fish_taimen_descr">The largest representatives in the salmon family, reaching 2 meters length and 80 kg weight. Freshwater fish, they never swim into the sea.</text>
   <text id="victory_day_5_3">	Catch fish for a certain total weight	</text>
   <text id="quest_11_9_1">Cast your line several last times in the Amazon!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_10">To River Valley!</text>
   <text id="victory_day_9_3">	Make several casts with your fishing rod!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc1_descr_1">Catch Crucians: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc3_descr_8">Catch [amount] Gold Crucians at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_tutorial_comics_text7">	Change the bait to catch a bigger fish!	</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_wood_rod">A rod for rookie anglers. Allows you to catch standard fish. The fishing rod is designed for fish weighing up to 1 kg.</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer0">The main goal of the game is to visit all playable locations and catch all fish that can be found there. To do that, the player has to complete a variety of quests and become a real professional of fishing!
    </text>
   <text id="quest_12_4_3">Silver spent on purchases will go to organize the festival!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_baikal_catfish">Amur catfish are a smaller relative of the common catfish. They are freshwater predators but can also be found in lightly-salted water. Amur catfish inhabit slow flowing waters, and in the summertime stick to arms on spates, in shore zones. In the autumn they leave for deeper reservoir areas, where they live a sedentary life. Amur catfish are valued for their outstanding gastronomic qualities: their tasty medium-fat meat with no bones.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_palia_ozern_descr">Lake Paly looks like a trout, but do not be fooled - in his heart it is the most natural char. It only lives in a lake  and rarely noticed in the river.</text>
   <text id="str_shop_unlock_location">Unlock location</text>
   <text id="quest_8_9">Rod Test</text>
   <text id="str_spin_free">Spin for free</text>
   <text id="str_location_welcome">Welcome to location </text>
   <text id="halloween_2_desc">Some fighters against evil spirits complained on the shortage of silver balls! </text>
   <text id="quest_1_4_desc">Today the Mayor will come to dine at Uncle Joe's. And you know what? He is fond of fish! That means, we have an order!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_4">Weight Class</text>
   <text id="halloween_2"> Silver Balls </text>
   <text id="entity_inhibitor_progress_title">	Catch scale down	</text>
   <text id="str_update_nothing">You have the latest version</text>
   <text id="str_spin_friends">Number of friends</text>
   <text id="victory_day_6">	Guerrilla Detachment	</text>
   <text id="halloween_8_3"> Catch Amur catfish on the total weight 16 kg! </text>
   <text id="victory_day_1_2">	Catch fish for a certain total weight.	</text>
   <text id="quest_5_8">For Science Sake!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_gidra_descr">Under the water, this lure moves abruptly and resembles a big freshwater hydra. Larger omnivorous fish will be very impressed by it!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_4_3">Catch a necessary number of Basses.</text>
   <text id="str_comics2">&quot;Hi! It's been a while! Please, come!&quot;</text>
   <text id="str_remove_fishnet">Remove FishNet</text>
   <text id="str_pause_resume">Resume</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_kuznechik">Grasshopper</text>
   <text id="quest_5_6_3">Catch some Atlantic Salmon!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_5_desc">The fisherman named Mourne says he was taught how to fish in a secret facility. No one can beat him... Only one eay to find that out!</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_your_place">Your place</text>
   <text id="str_fish_golavl">Chub</text>
   <text id="str_quest_104_text">I bet my [fish type] is bigger than yours! You'll never catch anything like this!</text>
   <text id="str_terms_head2">User Content</text>
   <text id="str_inv_inf">inf</text>
   <text id="quest_11_4_2">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc13_descr_8"> Catch [amount] Lake Paly at least [weight] </text>
   <text id="entity_accelerator_fish">	Speeds up the motion of the fish for some time - it becomes more difficult to catch it.	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_9">First Steps - Catch your first [amount] fishes!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_vendace">Vendace mainly inhabit lakes, are less commonly found in rivers, but are also caught in cold European seas. They prefer clear sandy or loamy bottoms and swim in lakes mainly in depths that allow them to avoid water that is too warm. Despite their small size, vendace are a desirable catch. They can be eaten fresh, salted or smoked and their caviar is also edible.</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_tournament_title">1500 Tournament</text>
   <text id="str_quest_101_text">The cat has run out of food. Catch any [quantity] fries for its lunch.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc12_descr_6">Catch Catfish on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_12_6_desc">National Zoo workers are amazed at the number of rare species inhabiting this area and ask you to catch more for them!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_10_2">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total! You'll need something to eat during the journey!</text>
   <text id="str_amulet_proposal_name_1">Silver Amulet</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_devil">Hell-fish</text>
   <text id="quest_1_5_3">Catch Ruffs weighing a specific total.</text>
   <text id="quest_7_7_1">Catch some Hunchbacks!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_4">Silver Bells</text>
   <text id="str_fish_lenta_descr">Elegant and graceful, the ribbon-shaped fish is the embodiment of honor and glory. This is a truly holiday fish!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_7">Fish Stockpile</text>
   <text id="quest_9_7_2">Use the Spinning spoonbait!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_3_1">Catch some American Catfish!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc10_descr_3">Catch Ocellate River Stingrays: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_9_4_1">Use the Middler rod.</text>
   <text id="str_quest_41_text">The neighbor has returned from fishing, bringing [quantity] [fish type] weighing at least [weight] each. Wanna fight?</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc11_descr_5">Catch a Chum Salmon on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_6_7_2">Catch some fish weighing 5 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="og_open_victory_river">What could be better than the smell of gunpowder and the heat of a tank engine? The answer is clear – a fat and hostile fish! Only I can pass this test of tenacity, patience, and strength!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_6_desc">Some fish can be seen only in this river! One can barely believe such ones can possibly exist!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc0_descr_0">Catch bleaks: [amount]</text>
   <text id="entity_accelerator_base_score">	Basic points decrease twice faster for some time.	</text>
   <text id="victory_day_7_desc">	Strengthen units with Bayonet-Fish – and the river general will be ready to attack with his army!	</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_novaya_descr">Larva</text>
   <text id="str_fish_shuka">Pike</text>
   <text id="str_fish_tench">Tench are quite large fish, which prefer to stick to silent river banks, oxbows, and quiet channels filled with underwater plants. They tend to be found in large rushes or reeds in lakes and murky ponds. Tench eat a lot of different types of food.</text>
   <text id="quest_15_2_2">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_ration">MRE, or a Meal Ready-to-Eat has that special combination of nutrients so loved by war-like fish. It is ideal for catching armored fish!</text>
   <text id="str_tutorial_comics_text2">	It's easy! Click on the hook to start fishing!	</text>
   <text id="quest_bonus_1">	Fishing!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_pirania_descr">River hyenas&quot; - this is how they are called due to their voracity. It's common that crocodiles run away upon spotting a group of piranhas. This fish has sharp, strong teeth, which can bite off sturdy hooks.</text>
   <text id="quest_3_1">Wild Things</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc12_descr_9">Catch a rare Lampern at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_2_6_1">Silver spent on purchases will go to pay for permission!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_army">Army rod</text>
   <text id="str_energy2">Normal tonic</text>
   <text id="str_comics1">I wish I could be out of town right now…</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc12_descr_8">Catch [amount] Zonders at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_me">me</text>
   <text id="new_year_11_3">	You need to try hard — cast your line several times!	</text>
   <text id="quest_11_6_3">Catch some Dogfish!</text>
   <text id="str_atlas_weight1">Weight: %.2f %s</text>
   <text id="quest_6_4_desc">I've found official registers containing local record. I bet we can do better!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_1">Bells Tolling</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_parenie_zerna">Steamed corn</text>
   <text id="quest_15_2_1">Use the Longlass 2000 rod.</text>
   <text id="quest_2_6_desc">You need a special permission to catch Bitterlings in this area!</text>
   <text id="str_shop_gold_no_bonus">No Bonus</text>
   <text id="str_comics4">Okay, I'll take only the most necessary things…</text>
   <text id="quest_7_8">Legend of Chum Salmon</text>
   <text id="quest_3_7_1">Silver spent on purchases will go to pay the road!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_5_3">Catch some Goldfish weighing 1.5 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_46_text">I've just read the fishermen's horoscope, it says if you catch [quantity] [fish type] weighing at least [weight], good luck will be with to you all year!</text>
   <text id="entity_silver_coin_title">	Silver coin	</text>
   <text id="quest_15_6_1">Catch some Openerfish!</text>
   <text id="str_location_lesnaya_rechushka">Pinery River</text>
   <text id="str_ok_title">Пригласи друга</text>
   <text id="quest_1_4_2">Catch a necessary number of Crucian Carps.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_sordelka_descr">Belongs to the Beer-Vodka species, a member of the Oktoberfest family, mainly inhabits the drainage systems of brewery works. The perfect snack with unfiltered beer! </text>
   <text id="str_najivka_spoon"> Spoon </text>
   <text id="str_fish_gold_crucian">Gold or yellow crucians are longstanding inhabitants of ponds, stagnant water lakes, oxbows and even small swamps. A gold crucian has a long, almost round body, red-copper sides and dark-red fins. Gold crucianscan reach half a meter in length and up to 5 kg in weight. In overpopulated reservoirs they become tiny - little larger than small coins. Gold crucians are known for their toughness and  ability to live in habitats with little oxygen in the water.</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_show_me">Show me</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_cherviak">Chopped Worm</text>
   <text id="halloween_5_2"> Catch cohos at least 1.85 kg! </text>
   <text id="str_fish_krasn_som">Redtail catfish</text>
   <text id="quest_11_1_3">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_already_chosen">The item has already been chosen</text>
   <text id="str_alert_rod_is_broken">Your rod is broken.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_bober_descr">A strange hybrid between a Spike and a pig. Sorry, between a beaver and a vobla. The furry vobla or flippered beaver - it's up to you to decide. It will look great when stuffed and hung on the wall or spread on the floor as a hallway mat. It is better left uneaten.</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_hyper_desc">Hyperloop Series always offer something original on the fishing tackle market. Thousands of fishermen have already caught 10 kg fish with this!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc14_descr_2">Catch Bottler on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_igrushki_descr">Stuffed bears, stuffed rabbits, and stuffed elephants! After washing and cleaning them they may be presented to your wife or girl! Indeed, why waste money? You'd better buy a spinning lure and bait!</text>
   <text id="str_30th_title">Attention!</text>
   <text id="quest_9_6_desc">A professor studying the Probability Theory suggests that you try catch as much fish as you can in a day!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc1_descr_3">Catch Sabres: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_trout">Trout are very peculiar fish. They are extremely shy, therefore you need to be very careful when approaching the bank. Trout are so fussy that it is extremely hard to select the right bait. Usually, trout inhabit small swift rivers full of crystal clear water, numerous obstacles,and habitats which are inaccessible or swampy. An interesting fact: trout are introduced into wastewater filtration systems, because they are sensitive to pollution. If toxic substances appear, these fish perish first. This is a type of natural warning system.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_rachok">Crustacean</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc1_descr_2">Catch Blue Breams: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_shop_tab_tools" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Tools</text>
   <text id="str_fish_artrodir_descr">A monstrous creature, the terror of the deeps. Looks suspiciously like certain extinct species... This predator eagerly attacks whales and sharks, although it will eat anything it finds. Apparently, this miraculously preserved giant gave birth to the Loch Ness legend.</text>
   <text id="str_uncatched_title">You need stronger rod</text>
   <text id="str_energy1_descr">Adds energy and allows for catching fish 5 percent larger</text>
   <text id="str_fish_podleshik">Small Bream</text>
   <text id="str_location_rocky_bay">The rocky mountains at sunset are definitely worth seeing! The sun disappears over the horizon in a haze, bathing Rocky Bay in beautiful hues. At moments like this, you will definitely forget all about the fish!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_gorbusha">Humpback Salmon</text>
   <text id="quest_11_1_2">Catch fish weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="quest_8_8">Fishing Club</text>
   <text id="quest_5_5_1">Catch some Goldfish!</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_no_connection">No connection</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc5_descr_6">Catch Burbot on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_location_lesnaya_zavod">Wildwood Pool</text>
   <text id="str_high">Big</text>
   <text id="str_day">Day</text>
   <text id="new_year_15_1">	Spend some silver on a Christmas Tree for children!	</text>
   <text id="new_year_3_desc">	Let's start our Christmas saving mission and send greeting cards to all friends and relatives! 	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_tilapia">Tilapia</text>
   <text id="quest_8_6_desc">Uncle Joe's birthday will be very soon... A pure silver figurine would be a great gift!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_7_3">Bring some new species for aquariums: Catch some Zanders!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_morozko">Froster fish</text>
   <text id="str_fish_mirror_carp">Mirror carp have a distinctive feature compared to common carp - their scale has separate large patches - &quot;mirrors&quot;, from which the name of the species originates.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_usuall">Simple spoon</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_middler_pro">Improved spinning of the Middler series. The spinning is more reliable, stronger and allows you to catch fish weighing up to 5 kg. </text>
   <text id="str_policy_head9">Policy Regarding Children</text>
   <text id="quest_11_7_2">Catch some Corwins!</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_krahmal_descr">If you want to catch some large fish, you should definitely use starch! Bigger fish go crazy for it!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_6">Fishing Permission</text>
   <text id="quest_2_5_3">Catch some European Carps weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc9_descr_2">Catch a Battalion fish: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_uncatched_approximate">approximate weight: %.2f %s</text>
   <text id="new_year_5_2">	Catch some Siberian Roaches weighing 0.3 kg each for a special dish!	</text>
   <text id="quest_13_2_2">Catch some Breams weighing at least 1 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_4_4">Use the Wood rod.</text>
   <text id="str_new_level_post1">Do you wonder why am I so happy? Got new level on Gone Fishing!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_6_2">Catch some Osmans!</text>
   <text id="str_location_velikie_ozera">Mountain Lake</text>
   <text id="quest_7_7_2">Catch some Arctic Ciscos!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_progress">	PROGRESS	</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_new_year">	Ice Rod	</text>
   <text id="quest_13_7_1">Catch some Ides in the Northern Donets!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_amur_som">Amur Catfish</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc10_descr_5">Catch Payara on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_14_5_3">Catch fish weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="quest_8_1">First Catch</text>
   <text id="quest_4_4_1">Catch some Marbled Sculpins!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_6_desc">The Laboratory asks you to catch Ruffs in different habitats!</text>
   <text id="str_shop_tab_rod" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Rods</text>
   <text id="str_location_lochness">Loch Ness Secret</text>
   <text id="quest_4_5_1">Catch some Golden Crucians!</text>
   <text id="victory_day_6_3">	Catch fish for a certain total weight	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc5_descr_5">Catch Zonder on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_catfish_imp">Catfish are active night predators preferring to wait out the daytime in cavities, under snags and floating rush isles. The diet of younger catfish includes small crustaceans, hatchlings and water insects. Older catfish prefer eating live fish and other freshwater creatures as well as shell-fish, depending on what's available. Catfish can grow extremely large - the largest documented catch was 952 lbs!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc14_descr_7">Catch [amount] Opener-fish at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_fb_req_message">Give %s a hand</text>
   <text id="victory_day_3_desc">	&quot;Report!&quot; – squeaks river general in your hands. After a long conversation, you realize that at the bottom of the river a real war is brewing.	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc13_descr_1"> Catch Carp: [amount] </text>
   <text id="quest_12_6">Variety of Species</text>
   <text id="quest_7_2">Invitation</text>
   <text id="quest_6_9_1">Catch some Asps.</text>
   <text id="halloween_3_desc"> Due to Halloween the popularity of scary fish has greatly increased! It's a great opportunity to earn! </text>
   <text id="quest_13_1_desc">Don't the bells scare fish away, I wonder? Let's check this out!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_7">Aquarium</text>
   <text id="quest_2_10_3">Pay the fisherman with silver to make him more approachable.</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_net1_descr"> Quality usual net with small cells. It is used for amateur fishing.  It's too difficult to catch something big with this net - both because of the small size of cells and the material not designed for big strong fish. </text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_bober">Voblabeaver</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_plotvichka_descr">Even the most cautious pike will never distinguish this large metal lure from an easily swimming roach. Once this lure swims past, a predator undoubtedly attacks it! </text>
   <text id="str_fish_catfish">Catfish are active night predators preferring to wait out the daytime in cavities, under snags and floating rush isles. The diet of younger catfish includes small crustaceans, hatchlings and water insects. Older catfish prefer eating live fish and other freshwater creatures as well as shell-fish, depending on what's available. Catfish can grow extremely large - the largest documented catch was 432 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_weight_kg"> kg</text>
   <text id="quest_3_7">Learn by Comparison</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer3">In order to win a mini-game, you need to keep the moving object inside the circle for a specified amount of time. Touch the screen to move the circle. After you succeed, you'll get your catch!
    </text>
   <text id="str_fish_podust">Nase</text>
   <text id="quest_3_1_3">Catch some Thornies!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_10_desc">Our next destination is the Sand Ridge. It'll not be so easy to get there!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_10_desc">We've got a new destination on our map: the legendary River Valley! Let's prepare for the journey!</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question16">How can I complete a Quest?
    </text>
   <text id="new_year_13_1">	Catch fish weighing 5 kg in total on the Sunset Coast.	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc4_descr_7">Catch [amount] Ciscos at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_fish_zerkalny_karp">Mirror carp</text>
   <text id="quest_3_9_desc">It's time to test some spoonbaits in such harsh conditions!</text>
   <text id="str_athlas_buy_info">Buy Info</text>
   <text id="str_quest_34_text">To cook great fish soup you need at least [quantity] [fish type]!</text>
   <text id="quest_12_1_1">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_belyi_amyr">White Amur</text>
   <text id="quest_9_3_1">Catch some Artrodirs!</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_sahar">Sugar</text>
   <text id="str_terms_head0">Accepting the Terms</text>
   <text id="str_fish_okun_pavlin">Yellow peacock</text>
   <text id="quest_4_8">Competition!</text>
   <text id="quest_9_10_desc">A local fisherman told you about the Victory river! Fancy going there?</text>
   <text id="str_notif_day_text">The morning came. It's time to catch daytime fishes!</text>
   <text id="str_atlas_record0">My personal record is: %2.3f%s</text>
   <text id="str_quest_50_text">I've got [fish type] here and they're biting like hell - I have caught [total weight] already! Can you do the same?</text>
   <text id="quest_11_8">Best Fisherman</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_remove">Net was removed</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc3_descr_6">Catch Osman on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc4_descr_2">Catch Blue Breams: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_4_6_desc">Uncle Joe urgently needs fish for his café, and nobody can help him but us!</text>
   <text id="str_fb_gift_title">Help received</text>
   <text id="quest_9_5_1">Catch some Sturgeons!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc10_descr_7">Catch [amount] Redtail Catfish at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc8_descr_1">Catch Pikes: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_shop_silver">silver coins</text>
   <text id="quest_10_2_1">Catch some Bitterlings!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc7_descr_6">Catch Baikal Grayling on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_9_2_2">Catch some Chars.</text>
   <text id="str_check">Check</text>
   <text id="quest_1_9_3">Earn some gold: we can't start off on a journey without enough money to cover expenses!</text>
   <text id="halloween_2_3"> Silver spent on purchases will go to the silver balls production! </text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer14">Use the Location Viewer to check out Fish details and learn what lures and baits you need catch it.
    </text>
   <text id="str_location_mountain_lake">What could be better than fishing in the fresh mountain air, on the shores of a lake filled with crystal-clear water set among magnificent rocks and delightful nature! Oh, there is trout here!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_snow">Snow-fish</text>
   <text id="str_fish_ayha_descr">The Chinese Perch, or 'Mandarin fish', is listed in the Red book and is popular in China. It is a voracious, carnivorous fish - even more ravenous than the pike. Feeds on other fish only.</text>
   <text id="new_year_6_2">	Catch some fish in a new location.	</text>
   <text id="quest_13_1_2">Catch fish weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="quest_3_8_2">Catch some Barbels weighing 7 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_1_desc">Try to reach an absolute harmony by fishing and enjoying the landscape at the same time!</text>
   <text id="victory_day_2_desc">	Looking closer, you realize that in this river live absolutely incredible creation. And it looks like they have a leader !	</text>
   <text id="quest_12_1_2">Catch fish weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="quest_1_3_3">Catch roaches weighing 1.5 kg in total</text>
   <text id="halloween_5_1"> Catch some cohos! </text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_set">Net was set</text>
   <text id="str_fish_tambakyi">Tambaqui</text>
   <text id="quest_5_7_1">Catch some Rudds weighing at least 0.75 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_location_elovii_descr">Somewhere deep in the mountain forests of northern Russia is a secluded lake, famous for its perfect fishing conditions. Locals call it Fir shore. It lies far from civilization, so beware of wild animals. It's said that packs of wolves roam the area...</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc5_descr_3">Catch Pikes at least: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_3_9_1">Use the &quot;A piece of iron&quot; spoonbait.</text>
   <text id="quest_3_4_desc">They say, there are unique herbs growing in this area. Local herbologists will appreciate if we bring back some samples!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_9_2">Catch some Mirror Carps in the Loch Ness!</text>
   <text id="quest_12_3">Championship</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc2_descr_8">Catch Freshwater Eels at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_ruff">Ruff are rather small bottom dwelling fish, which are not very fussy in terms of food and habitat selection. They feed on small fish, invertebrates, and algae. The dorsal fin of a ruff has sharp spines, so be careful when taking a ruff off your hook!</text>
   <text id="str_daily_bonus_gr">Congrats!</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_net0_descr"> Usual net with small cells . It is used for amateur fishing. It's too difficult to catch something big with this net - both because of the small size of cells and the material not designed for big strong fish. </text>
   <text id="str_fish_shipovka">Chipper</text>
   <text id="quest_8_2_3">Catch some Amur Carps.</text>
   <text id="quest_11_3_desc">The local tribe has been suffering from attacks of a monsterfish for some years. We have to stop that monster!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc12_descr_0">Catch Chubs: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_new_level_share_button">Share</text>
   <text id="quest_4_10_1">Silver spent on purchases will go to pay the road!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_araya_descr">Extremely dangerous. Posess one of the most powerful electric charges of all known animals in our world. A sudden charge can knock down even a sturdy fisherman.</text>
   <text id="entity_inhibitor_progress">	Decreases indication of the green catch scale.	</text>
   <text id="victory_day_5_desc">	Desperate Penal Battalion-Fish – the core of the river general army! But they are scattered all over the river, and no one can bring them together. Though…	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_amur_sazan">Amur Carp</text>
   <text id="str_quest_20_text">I've read that a fish diet is really healthy! But all the fish in the shop are really expensive. Catch any fish for me, but the bigger, the better!</text>
   <text id="quest_9_6">Probability Theory</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_plotvichka">Roach</text>
   <text id="str_fish_grass_pike">Grass pike, unlike their larger relatives, deep-water pike, hunt close to surface, rather than near the bottom. Laying in dense algae, a grass pike  waits for a fish swimming by and then pounces. That is why they are easy to catch with a bright lure skillfully launched near reeds.</text>
   <text id="quest_11_3_2">Catch a Piranha weighing 1.5 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_9_2">Earn some silver: we'll need money for the future!</text>
   <text id="quest_11_8_desc">A local tribe has announced a competition to find the best fisherman. We've been invited to participate!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_5">National Zoo</text>
   <text id="str_terms_text6">You agree that your use of the Service shall be at your sole risk. To the fullest extent permitted by law, Drimmi LLC, its Affiliates, officers, directors, employees, and agents disclaim all warranties, express or implies, in connection with the website and your use thereof including implied warranties of title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose or non-infringement, accuracy, authority, completeness, usefulness, and timeliness. Drimmi LLC makes no warranties or representations about the accuracy or completeness of the content of the Service and of the content of any sites linked to the Service; Drimmi LLC assumes no liability or responsibility for any (i) errors, mistakes, or inaccuracies of content, (ii) personal injury or property damage, of any nature whatsoever, resulting from your access to and use of the Service, (iii) any unauthorized access to or use of our secure servers and/or any and all personal information and/or financial information stored therein, (iv) any interruption or cessation of transmission to or from the Service, (v) any bugs, viruses, trojan horses, or the like which may be transmitted to or through the Service by any third party, and/or (vi) any errors or omissions in any content or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any content posted, emailed, transmitted, or otherwise made available via the Service.                  In no event will Drimmi LLC, its Affiliates, directors, officers, agents, contractors, partners and employees, be liable to you or any third person for any special, direct, indirect, incidental, special, punitive, or consequential damages whatsoever including any lost profits or lost data arising from your use of the Service or other materials on, accessed through or downloaded from the Service, whether based on warranty, contract, tort, or any other legal theory, and whether or not Drimmi LLC has been advised of the possibility of these damages. The foregoing limitation of liability shall apply to the fullest extent permitted by law in the applicable jurisdiction. You specifically acknowledge that Drimmi LLC shall not be liable for user submissions or the defamatory, offensive, or illegal conduct of any third party and that the risk of harm or damage from the foregoing rests entirely with you.                  You agree to indemnify and hold Drimmi LLC, and each of its Affiliates, directors, officers, agents, contractors, partners and employees, harmless from and against any loss, liability, claim, demand, damages, costs and expenses, including reasonable attorney's fees, arising out of or in connection with (i) your use of and access to the Service; (ii) your violation of any term of these Terms of Service; (iii) your violation of any third party right, including without limitation any copyright, property, or privacy right; (iv) any claim that one of your User Submissions caused damage to a third party; or (v) any Content you post or share on or through the Service.</text>
   <text id="str_closed">Locked</text>
   <text id="str_fish_usach">Barb</text>
   <text id="str_tired_fish_lose">Lose</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_net3"> Quality strong net </text>
   <text id="str_ok_invite">Пригласить</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_molusk">Mollusk</text>
   <text id="quest_1_3_desc">A fisherman from the tavern sweared he managed to catch a giant roach. Let's check whether it's possible or not!	</text>
   <text id="og_open_wild_shore">There was not a single person for miles around. Despite the fact that I had to struggle through dense thickets, I was smiling. I was the first to reach that lost backwater!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_10_2">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total! You'll need something to eat during the journey!</text>
   <text id="quest_12_7_desc">A laboratory is conducting a research and asks you to catch some fish from different habitats!</text>
   <text id="quest_12_5_desc">The National Zoo asks you to catch some rare local fish!</text>
   <text id="str_quest">Quest</text>
   <text id="str_shop_amulet_title">Amulet of Luck</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc11_descr_1">Catch Humpback Salmons: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_12_3_3">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_lineika">Ruler-fish</text>
   <text id="og_open_amazon">I was repeatedly warned of how dangerous the local tribes could be, but the thirst for exotics has prevailed. The rapid flow of tropical rivers and the alluring appeal of the Amazon water bodies bid defiance to my persistence. Well, let's see who wins!</text>
   <text id="new_year_5">	Save the Honey Shore!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_sig">Cisco</text>
   <text id="quest_10_9_1">Catch some Mirror Carps in the Victory River!</text>
   <text id="str_fb_invite_friends">Invite friends!</text>
   <text id="victory_day_6_1">	Catch some Guerrilla-Fish to raise assault units.	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc13_descr_4"> Catch Goldfish on total weight [summ weight] </text>
   <text id="str_quest_requirenments">Will facilitate fishing</text>
   <text id="str_bank_awaiting">Connecting to AppStore</text>
   <text id="quest_12_7">Research</text>
   <text id="str_market_cancel">No, Thanks</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_first_prize_description">100 gold coins</text>
   <text id="quest_7_4_3">Catch some Ciscos on the Sunset Coast!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_3">Equipment Test</text>
   <text id="str_fish_gone" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="36">Fish got away ...</text>
   <text id="quest_10_1_3">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_9_3">Catch some Basses in the Forest River!</text>
   <text id="str_update_get">Downloading update...</text>
   <text id="quest_1_7_1">Catch Uncle Joe's lucky card!</text>
   <text id="quest_15_6_3">Catch Openerfish weighing 6 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_8_1">Catch the most Barbels!</text>
   <text id="str_fb_req_title">Help your friend</text>
   <text id="str_uncatched_too_heavy">was too heavy for your rod</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_middler">The pearl among the rods for beginners. The price is moderated by high quality and reliability. With this rod you can now catch a really big fish! The largest bearable fish may even exceed 4  kg specified by the manufacturer.</text>
   <text id="quest_9_10_1">Cast your line several last times in the Loch Ness!</text>
   <text id="new_year_6_desc">	Uncle Joe invited us to celebrate Christmas on the Snowy Shore, you need to see that!	</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_obuv_descr">Don't be in a hurry to get rid of the old boots and shoes you catch. What if, after fishing out one shoe from a pair you later catch the other? It could make a great present for your mother-in-law on her birthday!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_5">National Park Order</text>
   <text id="str_30th_text">As we've changed the level system you have a free possibility to reset your experience to the first level. However all your gold will be kept and you'll get a possibility to get levels with rewards!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_2_3">Catch fish weighing 4 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_quest_40_text">Guests are going to be plump! But there's nothing to stand on. It would be great if you caught [quantity] [fish type]. But each fish shouldn't be under [weight]</text>
   <text id="str_ok_sending_ok">Приглашения разосланы. Спасибо!</text>
   <text id="str_policy_head2">Other Disclosure of Your Personal Information </text>
   <text id="victory_day_10_2">	Catch a Tank-Fish heavier than 7.3 kg.	</text>
   <text id="quest_12_6_2">Catch some Goldilocks!</text>
   <text id="quest_9_8_1">Catch some Danube Trouts!</text>
   <text id="halloween_1"> Hell-fish </text>
   <text id="str_fish_dorado_descr">These delicacies have numerous historical roots - they were even bred by ancient Romans! Until now, they are still the favorite fish of coastal nations. In turn, dorado favor shellfish and mollusks.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_motil">Bloodworm</text>
   <text id="quest_9_10">Victory River</text>
   <text id="quest_5_2">Reciprocal Gift</text>
   <text id="entity_accelerator_combo">	Increases the number of points earned for keeping the fish inside the circle.	</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_sleeve">This bait attracts tough fish only. The smell of war is what draws them!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_8_3">Catch some fish weighing a specific total.</text>
   <text id="quest_1_2">	Nets	</text>
   <text id="str_terms_text4">The Drimmi LLC Service may provide communication channels such as forums, communities, or chat areas (&quot;Communication Channels&quot;) designed to enable you to communicate with other Service users. Drimmi LLC has no obligation to monitor these communication channels but it may do so and reserves the right to review materials posted to the Communication Channels and to remove any materials, at any time, with or without notice for any reason, at its sole discretion. Drimmi LLC may also terminate or suspend your access to any Communication Channels at any time, without notice, for any reason. You acknowledge that chats, postings, or materials posted by users on the Communication Channels are neither endorsed nor controlled by Drimmi LLC, and these communications should not be considered reviewed or approved by Drimmi LLC. Drimmi LLC will not under any circumstance be liable for any activity within Communication Channels.                  You agree that all your communications with the Communication Channels are public, and thus you have no expectation of privacy regarding your use of the Communication Channels. Drimmi LLC is not responsible for information that you choose to share on the Communication Channels, or for the actions of other users.                  You agree that your use of the Service shall be lawful and that you will comply with the usage rules. In furtherance of the foregoing, and as an example and not as a limitation, you agree not to use the Service in order to:                                    - post, upload, transmit or otherwise disseminate information that is obscene, indecent, vulgar, pornographic, sexual or otherwise objectionable         - defame, libel, ridicule, mock, stalk, threaten, harass, intimidate or abuse anyone, hatefully, racially, ethnically or, in a reasonable person's view, otherwise offensive or objectionable         - upload or transmit (or attempt to upload or transmit) files that contain viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, cancelbots, corrupted files or data, or any other similar software or programs that may damage the operation of the Service or other users' computers         - violate the contractual, personal, intellectual property or other rights of any party including using, uploading, transmitting, distributing, or otherwise making available any information made available through the Service in any manner that infringes any copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, or other right of any party (including rights of privacy or publicity)         - attempt to obtain passwords or other private information from other members         - improperly use support channels or complaint buttons to make false reports to Drimmi LLC         - develop, distribute, or publicly inform other members of &quot;auto&quot; software programs, &quot;macro&quot; software programs or other &quot;cheat utility&quot; software program or applications in violation of the applicable License Agreements         - exploit, distribute or publicly inform other members of any game error, miscue or bug which gives an unintended advantage         - violate any applicable laws or regulations, or promote or encourage any illegal activity including, but not limited to, hacking, cracking or distribution of counterfeit software, or cheats or hacks for the Service</text>
   <text id="quest_4_8_desc">It's time to compete with the best local fishermen. Let the most able one win!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_elec">Dace</text>
   <text id="str_quest_45_text">The neighbor has returned from fishing, bringing [quantity] [fish type] weighing at least [weight] each. Wanna fight?</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_spoon_desc"> A cheaper equivalent of Shellfish spoon. A part of flatware that can be useful for a fisherman not only for dinner ! </text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_konfeta">Lollypop-fish</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_hour">h</text>
   <text id="new_year_10_2">	Catch some icy fish!	</text>
   <text id="str_quest_37_text">Remember how we used to catch [fish type] together? Let's recreate those times and get [quantity]!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_Ide">Although Ide are freshwater fish, they can live in the lightly-salted waters of estuaries. They inhabit rivers and lakes, preferring gently flowing deep backwaters with loamy ground, they feed on prey moving to strong current areas. Ide are omnivores and feed early in the morning. Their diet consists of vegetables and animal food (insects, shell-fish and worms).</text>
   <text id="str_comics6">&quot;I haven't seen you for ages!&quot;</text>
   <text id="quest_10_5_2">Catch some Thornbacks!</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_yantar">Amber stones</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question1">What do I have to do?
    </text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_soldatiki_descr">The set of fished-out toy soldiers might be presented to your little son on his birthday, and the money you save could be spent on a new fishing rod or used to linger over drinks with your friends in a pub!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_2_1">Catch some Bleaks!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc7_descr_0">Catch Sabres: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_common_carp">Common carp usually feed on water plants, the spawn of early spawning fish and frogs in the spring and early summer. In the summertime their diet slightly changes - the basic food at that time includes water insects, worms, small snails, spatterdocks, molting crayfish, small leeches, etc. Common carp are long-living fish, some species living as long as 35-40 years.</text>
   <text id="quest_9_5_3">Catch Sturgeons weighing 8 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_novaya">Larva</text>
   <text id="str_quest_buy">Finish</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_paek">MRE</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_brelki">Key fobs</text>
   <text id="str_fb_messages_accept">Accept</text>
   <text id="str_shop_amulet_text">Put on the amulet and all fish will be 10% bigger!</text>
   <text id="str_inventory_equip" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Use</text>
   <text id="str_policy_head5">Links</text>
   <text id="str_tutorial_comics_text4">	Pull now!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_keta">Chum</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_connecting">Connecting</text>
   <text id="str_fish_olivk_som_descr">Olive Catfish is a quite popular object of fishing, highly regarded for the taste of meat. It lives in rivers and lakes of North America. This predator, able to reach up to 1.5 meters in length.</text>
   <text id="str_quest_grand_reward">Great Reward</text>
   <text id="quest_1_3_1">Catch a roach weighing at least 0.1 kg. Hints below will show you what to do!	</text>
   <text id="quest_1_5_desc">Local fishermen tell each other stories of a giant ruff. Many have seen it in cloudy waters, but no one managed to catch it!</text>
   <text id="tut_1_1">	Back in Business	</text>
   <text id="new_year_14_2">	Catch some snowy fish!	</text>
   <text id="new_year_1_2">	Cast your line several times for a great fishing!	</text>
   <text id="str_apology_text">Dear players! 
During the latest updates in the game have been many changes that could affect the gameplay and maintaining progress of the players. We sincerely apologize for any inconvenience caused and would like to make a gift for You. Have a nice fishing! 
Sincerely, the team Gone Fishing.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_chervyak">Earthworm</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_gidra">Hydra</text>
   <text id="quest_6_2_desc">It seems, local cooks like fish dishes... I smell an opportunity to earn some money!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_3">Fish Day</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question4">What do I need lures and baits for?
    </text>
   <text id="new_year_6_3">	Catch some fish weighing 7 kg in total.	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_bichok_krugl">Round goby</text>
   <text id="quest_9_2_desc">Let's give some fish to the guardian of the lake in order to win his favour!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_9_desc">The lab is conducting an urgent research and needs some Basses from different habitats!</text>
   <text id="str_location_block_unlock">Unlock</text>
   <text id="quest_11_9_desc">It was too hot there, it's high tome to go into some cool coniferous forest! Let's go to the Fir Coast!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_general_descr">The boss at the bottom of the sea! The Commander-In-Chief over cannoneer-fish and seahorses. It is difficult to catch, because it is always escorted by bodyguards. It tastes pretty good, but is a bit tough…</text>
   <text id="quest_12_4_desc">Locals want to organize an open-air festival, but they need some fish dishes!</text>
   <text id="str_daily_bonus_yg">You get: </text>
   <text id="str_fish_asp">Asps inhabit rivers, avoiding stagnant waters. They prefer to float close to the surface. Young asp fish feed on worms and insects, adults also eat small fish. Having toothless jaws, asp catch small fish usually by knocking them unconscious and then simply picking them up.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc6_descr_0">Catch Vendecas: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_1_1_4">Catch the right amount of perch!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_yaz">Ide</text>
   <text id="quest_12_7_3">Catch some Blue Breams on the Honey Coast!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc6_descr_3">Catch Minnows: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_nautilus">Nautilus</text>
   <text id="str_shop_gold_best_val1">BEST</text>
   <text id="quest_14_6_2">Catch an Olive Catfish weighing 0.35 kg!</text>
   <text id="halloween_3"> Halloween! </text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_net4"> Big net </text>
   <text id="victory_day_4_3">	Use some bait to  alarm a signal detachment!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_flat_bream">Flat bream  are shoaling fish in the carp family, related closely to bream. With a silvery, heavily side-flattened body they are reminiscent of young bream. Flat bream differ from common bream only by the number and location of teeth. They have seven teeth in two rows.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc12_descr_2">Catch Red-eyes: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_3_3_1">Catch some Rotans!</text>
   <text id="quest_1_6_5">Use the Grasshopper bait!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_minnow">Minnow inhabit fast flowing cold water rivers. They are the most important source of food for predatory fish. Somelake minnows have been kept in aquariums, but this is not possiblee for river minnow, as they need flowing water. Lake minnow bear low water oxygen and water oiliness well. They feed on gnat-worms, small flies, and breadcrumbs.</text>
   <text id="str_win_label_loginToPlay">Login to play with your friends</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc10_descr_2">Catch Piranhas: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_4_3_3">Use the Corn lure!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_osman">Osman</text>
   <text id="new_year_13_desc">	Some locations still wait for Christmas to come! We need to go there and bring the Spirit of Christmas with us!	</text>
   <text id="quest_4_6">Fish Order</text>
   <text id="str_fish_new">New page opened!</text>
   <text id="str_fb_inv_fr_title">Choose friends</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc4_descr_3">Catch Vimbas: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_gather_fishnet">Gather FishNet</text>
   <text id="str_fish_ice_descr">These incredible creatures can resist the lowest temperatures. Ice fish can survive in the coldest corners of the world.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_atlantic_sturgeon_descr">Despite being the largest members of the sturgeon family, they mainly feed on seafloor crustaceans, mollusks and small fish. The Atlantic variety could be considered the grandparents of the Sturgeon family, since they can reach100 years old. A critically endangered species, we don't advise fishing them up in real life..</text>
   <text id="str_fish_baikal_sig_descr">Baikal whitefish unlike other lake whitefish have low-height body and dense scales. Their main habitats are shallow waters with sandy ground. Adult Baikal whitefish feed on shell-fish, benthic gammaridea, planktonic crustaceans, insect larvae, worms, and young goby.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_norway_haddock">Norway haddock closely resemble perch in the shape of their body, however they are actually so different r that Norway haddock belong not only to another family, but to another order of spiny-finned fish. Coastal Norway haddock prefer to live where there is algae and stay in a small area without roaming far. They catch their prey - small fish, large crustaceans and other invertebrates swimming over the bottom - suddenly ambushing their prey.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_gylza">Bullet casing</text>
   <text id="victory_day_1">	Mystic River	</text>
   <text id="new_year_8_desc">	Wow! Do you see that, too? That's a fish wearing Santa costume! We need to catch it immediately and send to our laboratory!	</text>
   <text id="quest_4_1_1">Catch several Royal Fish!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_blesna_cherviak_descr">Moving under the water, this lure looks exactly like a large stream-driven worm. When seeing this tasty prey, most omnivorous fish immediately attack! </text>
   <text id="str_shop_gold_best_val2">VALUE</text>
   <text id="str_fish_polosat_som">Striped catfish</text>
   <text id="quest_14_2">Following the Master</text>
   <text id="str_policy_head10">Contacting Us</text>
   <text id="quest_12_5">National Zoo</text>
   <text id="quest_4_2_desc">Before we start fishing on a new spot, let's try to cast a line several times!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_1_3">Cast your line several times.</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_hyper">Sp. Hyperloop</text>
   <text id="str_fish_minoga_descr">Parasites, favoring large rivers and preferring a concealed way of life. Hooking a Lampern is a real rarity. They mainly feed on detritus and algae, but also sometimes small worms.</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_alcohol_descr">By the quantity of empty bottles one may assess the number of people who like to drink alcohol while fishing. And sometimes you may even catch a sealed bottle among the variety of empty ones! It's up to you what to do with this water gift - place it on a shelf as a memento or risk tasting it!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc12_descr_5">Catch Pike on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_elitesmpl">Sp. Elite Simple</text>
   <text id="quest_6_6_3">Catch some Ruffs in the Forest River!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_humpback_salmon">Humpback salmon are a species of anadromous fish in the salmon family. They are the smallest and most abundant species of Pacific salmon. Humpbacks are a valuable commercial fish species. Their meat is used for soup, braising, frying, salting and canning. Humpback caviar is also used in cookery for canning after salting.</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_longlass">Medium rod of the Longlass series. Needless to say, the quality and reliability of the tackle in this series are excellent. This tackle also allows you to easily catch fish weighing up to 35 kg.</text>
   <text id="quest_9_9">Lab Order</text>
   <text id="str_quest_31_text">The cat is such a fussy eater, it won't eat every kind of fish! Catch [quantity], it loves [fish type]!</text>
   <text id="str_new_level_post4">Rise and Shine. It's fishing time! New level up in Gone Fishing!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_baikal_osetr">Baikal Sturgeon</text>
   <text id="new_year_17_1">	Catch some Santa-fish!	</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_old_rod">Old beat-up rod from someone's attic. Allows you to catch  the smallest  fish. The fishing rod is slimpsy, so the rod is only for fish weighing up to 0.5 kg.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_zunder">Zander are typical ambush predators. They feed on fish, and younger species and also eat water invertebrates. They are very sensitive to oxygen concentration in the water and to the presence of suspended solids, which is why they avoid boggy reservoirs. Zander are active both day and night, but in the daytime they stay in shallow waters andat night move to deeper places. Zander meat is considered good for people dieting as it is full of protein and contains only a small amount of oil.</text>
   <text id="quest_14_3_2">Catch an American Catfish weighing 1.3 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_8_desc">The lab is conducting a comparative research and needs some Eels from different habitats!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_8_2">The 2nd rule: Catch some Sabrefish weighing 0.5 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc1_descr_9">Catch Rare Sky Gazer at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_10_2_2">Catch some Whitefish weighing 0.3 kg!!</text>
   <text id="str_amulet_proposal_desc_0">+5% weight</text>
   <text id="quest_11_5_1">Catch some Piraputangas!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_6">Silver Figurine</text>
   <text id="new_year_15_desc">	That's not fair! The students of local school are left without Christmas… We need to help them!	</text>
   <text id="new_year_1">	Winter Guest	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_rotan_descr">Short, dense body of this fish is covered with dull scales of medium size. Coloration is variable, dominated with gray-green and dirty brown color. Rotan – is a predator that eats fish spawn and fingerlingsleeches, newts, tadpoles. In a small pond rotan is becoming numerous and able to completely wipe out other species of fish. </text>
   <text id="str_policy_head4">Cookies</text>
   <text id="quest_5_1_desc">It's so beautiful here, like on a movie screen! I can't wait to catch the first fish!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_piavka">Leech</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_al_zhivec">Live bait</text>
   <text id="str_quest_new">NEW</text>
   <text id="new_year_18_1">	Catch more Asps than others!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_baikal_sig">Baikal Whitefish</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_udochka_descr">You come across the abandoned pieces of a rod in the lake. They can definitely be reassembled!</text>
   <text id="quest_bonus_1_3">	Catch fish weighing 0.4 kg in total!	</text>
   <text id="quest_2_8_2">Catch some Bersches!</text>
   <text id="quest_15_4_2">Catch a Barrelfish weighing 7 kg!</text>
   <text id="new_year_2_2">	Cast your line several times!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc0_descr_7">Catch Bream: [amount]</text>
   <text id="entity_placebo_title">	Blank sample	</text>
   <text id="str_shop_tab_udochki" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Rods</text>
   <text id="quest_7_8_3">Catch some Chum Salmon weighing 6 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_3_3">Catch some fish weighing 3 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_harius">Grayling</text>
   <text id="str_spin_exit">Play</text>
   <text id="quest_6_9_desc">The National Zoo needs some local species to enrich its variety!</text>
   <text id="new_year_10">	Sub Zero!	</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_staff">	Candy Cane	</text>
   <text id="quest_11_7_3">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="quest_10_1_2">Catch fish weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="halloween_1_3"> Catch hell-fish on the total weight 9 kg! </text>
   <text id="str_terms_head7">General</text>
   <text id="str_amulet_info_0">Bronze Amulet: Gives 5% increase to the weight of the catch!</text>
   <text id="str_location_thousand"> Thousand Islands </text>
   <text id="quest_5_9_3">Catch some Grass Pikes weighing at least 0.75 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question6">Are there any day/night changes?
    </text>
   <text id="victory_day_12_3">	Catch Ribbonfish for the total weight of 15 kg – the parade should be awesome!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_sordelka">Wiener-fish</text>
   <text id="str_salat_descr">Holiday lure designed for winter fish catching.</text>
   <text id="str_event_unlock">Выловите 15 билетов и разблокируйте локацию</text>
   <text id="halloween_6_2"> Catch Humpback Salmon at least 1.2 kg! </text>
   <text id="quest_6_7_1">Catch the necessary amount of fish!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_3_3">Catch American Catfish weighing 6 kg in total 6.</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question12">What are the Game Settings and how to change them?
    </text>
   <text id="quest_15_1_1">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_shemaya_descr">Shemaya is a genus of the carp family. Shemaya feed on crustaceans, insects, their larvae, worms and plankton. After reaching maturity at the age of 2-3, shemaya repeat the path of their parents. Shemaya are well-known for the taste and tenderness of their oily meat and they are most valuable commercial fish of the carp family. They are called &quot;shah mague&quot; (i.e. royal fish) in Persia.</text>
   <text id="quest_1_1_desc">Even the most experienced fishermen know that the right choice of tackles is half the battle. Let's prepare for fishing properly!	</text>
   <text id="quest_5_5_2">Catch a Goldfish weighing at least 0.43 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_6">Find Ruffs!</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question7">What is the &quot;Daily Spin&quot;?
    </text>
   <text id="quest_10_10_1">Cast your line several last times in the Victory River!</text>
   <text id="victory_day_11">	Peaceful settlement	</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_fb_login">Login with Facebook</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_derevyannaya">Wood Rod</text>
   <text id="victory_day_12_desc">	After a couple of hours the river has changed remarkably – the thankful inhabitants celebrate the end of the war joyfully jumping out of water!	</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_banki_descr">A can is the perfect place to store various types of bait! Don’t you know that? This is a time-tested old fishermen-proved method! Some anglers even collect lucky cans containing the bait that always makes fish bite!</text>
   <text id="str_fishlist_razdelitel_3">Funny</text>
   <text id="quest_15_4_desc">Look, there's a barrel floating near the coastвЂ¦ Ah, it's a Barrelfish! Let's catch it now!</text>
   <text id="victory_day_4">	Morse code	</text>
   <text id="str_btn_rodinout_tashit" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="33">Pull</text>
   <text id="str_market_title">Rate Gone Fishing</text>
   <text id="quest_4_5_desc">Huh? What is it there underwater? Ha! These are Golden and Silver Crucians! I know someone who can pay handsomely for them!</text>
   <text id="str_no_najivka" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="36">Please choose bait.</text>
   <text id="str_new_level_post0">Fishing is not a sport - it's a way of life! New level up in Gone Fishing!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_no_bite" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="36">Fish will not bite.</text>
   <text id="quest_7_10_2">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total! You'll need something to eat during the journey!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_lake_trout">Lake trout do not migrate, but stay in reservoirs for breeding and maturing. Lake trout may be found everywhere - in small mountain streamlets, flood rivers and powerful flowing rivers. Lake trout are strongly attached to their territory, especially those inhabiting rivers. Once a fish finds a place with an abundance of food it aggressively wards off any competitor daring to approach too closely. Lake trout choose positions which they consider most convenient and start hunting: they snatch insects, their larvae (stoneflies etc) and small crustaceans drifting by.</text>
   <text id="quest_5_4_desc">An environmentalist wants to buy back all the fish we catch to release it!</text>
   <text id="str_btn_rodinout_vitashit" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="33">Pull out</text>
   <text id="halloween_4_2"> Catch Rotans at least 0.7 kg! </text>
   <text id="str_fish_salmon">Salmon or so-called salmo salar are one of the most famous, spectacular and tasty species of the salmon family. These surprisingly big fish can reach up to 1.5 m long and weigh as much as 39 kg. Their regular diet usually includes such small creatures as crustaceans and other small-sized ocean fish.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_okun_pirat_descr">Pirate Perch - the only type of fish with a &quot;chemical&quot; camouflage, making it invisible for the fish. Spend mostly solitary life and loves to hunt at night. </text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc13_descr_9"> Catch Olive Catfish at least [weight] </text>
   <text id="quest_1_7_3">Cast your line several times.</text>
   <text id="quest_7_6_desc">A local hospital needs some toxin, which can be extracted only from a Shad, to prepare a medicine!</text>
   <text id="quest_15_4_3">Catch Barrelfish weighing 6 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_3_2">Use the Nubler Simple rod.</text>
   <text id="new_year_5_3">	Put some silver in the Christmas money box!	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc8_descr_6">Catch [amount] Lake trouts at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="day_number">Day %d</text>
   <text id="str_quest_54_text">There is nothing better than [fish type] cooked by a skilled chef! Catch [total weight] and find out for sure!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_9_2">Catch some Catfish.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc3_descr_7">Catch Chub on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="quest_11_6_1">Catch some Piraibas!</text>
   <text id="quest_9_3_desc">A friend of yours needs an impressive catch to make an impression on the barwoman in the inn!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_4_1">Catch some Ciscos in the River Valley!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_atlantich_osetr">Atlantic sturgeon</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc5_descr_1">Catch Volga Zonders: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_bleak">Bleak are small shoaling fish that live in almost in every river, lake or reservoir. They are characterized by loose scales that remain on your fingers when you touch them. Bleak are not particularly tasty.</text>
   <text id="str_location_river_valley">A fast coldwater  river  full of various types of fish and other river creatures flows through this sun-drenched green valley! Surely, it's better to come here with the whole family. It will be difficult for a lonely fisherman to catch and carry all those fish!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_baikal_omul">Baikal Omul</text>
   <text id="quest_4_4_2">Catch some Marbled Sculpins weighing at least 0.12 kg!</text>
   <text id="new_year_17_desc">	Local Zoo offers a reward for a set of fancy-dressed fish! Catch them all!	</text>
   <text id="str_catching_message6">GODLIKE!</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_prize_place">%d PLACE</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc0_descr_3">Catch Small Bream: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_8_9_1">Use the Goodfish S rod!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc6_descr_8">Catch [amount] Gralings at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_fish_peskar">Gudgeon</text>
   <text id="quest_2_3_2">Catch the most Pikes!</text>
   <text id="str_btn_rodinout_zakinut" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="33">Cast</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc8_descr_5">Catch Salmon on total weight [summ weight]</text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_0">Novice Fisherman - Get all achievements on Pinery River</text>
   <text id="quest_3_6">Gift for Uncle Joe</text>
   <text id="victory_day_6_desc">	Courage and experience make the Guerrilla-Fish excellent warriors in river wars! Their presence is the key to success in any campaign!	</text>
   <text id="quest_5_10_1">Silver spent on purchases will go to pay the road!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_106_text">Buddy, I've heard from my pals that there is a huge [fish type] somewhere over there! My friends are frettng that it will be caught by someone else. Now’s your chance, get it first!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_5_2">Buy some Clam baits</text>
   <text id="quest_7_9_2">Catch a Round Bullhead weighing at least 0.2 kg!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc8_descr_0">Catch Spirlins: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_13_4_2">Earn some silver!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_6">Fish Order</text>
   <text id="quest_11_5_3">Catch some Electric Eels!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_35_text">Small [fish type] are delicious. If you catch [quantity], I will cook them, yummy!</text>
   <text id="quest_8_5">Mourne Identity</text>
   <text id="quest_10_6_1">Catch some Penalfish!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_canal_som">Channel Catfish</text>
   <text id="quest_14_8_desc">It's time to leave this beautiful place for now. We haven't visited other corners of the world yet!</text>
   <text id="str_comics8">&quot;You know that I'm so passionate about fishing…&quot;</text>
   <text id="quest_12_6_3">Catch fish weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question8">What are Collections?
    </text>
   <text id="str_catching_message2">EXCELLENT!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_4_1">Catch some Carps!</text>
   <text id="quest_15_4_1">Catch some Barrelfish!</text>
   <text id="str_spin_days">Number of days</text>
   <text id="str_daily_bonus_wt">Your daily bonus is waiting!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc7_descr_7">Catch [amount] Amur Carps at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_location_volga">Honey Shore</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_listia_descr">Sometimes very beautiful leaves can be found in the water - they are worth using in a fine herbarium or drying between book pages for souvenirs.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_losos_dunaisk">Huchen</text>
   <text id="quest_2_10_1">Catch some Crucian Carps weighing at least 0.4 kg.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_grasshopper">Every skillful fisherman knows that if you plan to catch large river fish, there is nothing better than a grasshopper! One problem - this jumping bait also has to be captured.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc7_descr_3">Catch Baikal Omuls: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_7_3_desc">It's time to test our equipment on the new place!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_3">Legend of Thousand Islands</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_beastm_desc">Superior and professional rod with rings made of high module carbon. For amateurs of large and rare fish!</text>
   <text id="str_event_second">sec.</text>
   <text id="quest_5_2_2">Catch fish weighing 4 kg in total: that will look well as addition to Carps!</text>
   <text id="new_year_16_desc">	Laboratory assistants can't explain the sudden apparition of ball-fish and ask us to catch some samples!	</text>
   <text id="quest_13_1_3">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_2">Test Casting</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_mulaj_desc"> A cheaper equivalent of a Live Bait. The construction of several segments creates a false impression of a small fish in dirty water. </text>
   <text id="quest_14_1_2">Catch fish weighing 3 kg in total.</text>
   <text id="quest_4_10_3">Spend some gold to buy equipment: we'll need it!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_santa">Santa-fish</text>
   <text id="str_comics11">&quot;...go on a journey all alone. Fancy joining me?&quot;</text>
   <text id="str_quest_107_text">There's a guy's boasting about the [fish type] he's caught, I saw it, it's massive! But I believe in you – you can catch a bigger [fish type]!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_3">Equipment Test</text>
   <text id="new_year_16_1">	Catch some ball-fish!	</text>
   <text id="quest_11_4_1">Use the Longlass X rod.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_shar_descr">This underwater balloon is pretty tasty, especially when baked in a real Russian stove. And when correctly dried it imakes an excellent exotic Christmas tree toy.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc12_descr_10">Catch White Amur at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="str_notif_night_text">Twilight is approaching. Night fish are on the hunt!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_baikal_osetr_descr">Baikal sturgeon are evolutionarily the most ancient and largest fish of Lake Baikal. They are the only type of cartilaginous fish in Baikal, forming here a special subspecies. The color of a sturgeon varies from light-brown to dark-green-grey-brown, although the underside is always light. Small bony plates of various forms in between five rows of bony bucklers are situated along the body of a sturgeon. Baikal sturgeons feed on insects, young fish and invertebrates. </text>
   <text id="quest_8_1_2">Catch some fish weighing 5 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_nublsmt">Nubler Smart</text>
   <text id="str_fish_red_eye">Red-eye are often confused with another fish species, i.e. roach, but experienced fishermen know that the former differ from the latter by numerous signs, no need to look inside or under gills.A red-eye's scale is finer and has a golden shade. Also, these fish are thicker and fleshier, similar to breach rather than roach. Larger red-eye (above 800 g) gain deeper red color, sometimes their scale is filled with bloody color.</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_goodfishs">Goodfish S</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_round">	Candy	</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc12_descr_4">Catch Ides: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_location_amazon">Amazon</text>
   <text id="str_fish_dried"> Drytails</text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_6">Tireless Fisherman - Get all achievements on Secret Backwater</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc12_descr_3">Catch Asps: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc4_descr_8">Catch [amount] Salmons at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="victory_day_8_3">	Catch some Bayonet-Fish.	</text>
   <text id="str_shop_bank_title">Bank</text>
   <text id="str_shop_inf">free</text>
   <text id="new_year_9_desc">	We need to catch some herrings for a Christmas dish!	</text>
   <text id="new_year_1_desc">	Ho ho ho! Go fishing with me, I have plenty news for you!	</text>
   <text id="new_year_2_3">	Earn some silver — it can help you to solve many problems!	</text>
   <text id="quest_4_3">Elusive Reptile</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_goroh">Green Peas</text>
   <text id="victory_day_2_3">	Catch the most important General-Fish weighing 0.9 kg – this is a local leader!	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_lesh">Bream</text>
   <text id="str_fishnet_net5_descr"> You can put this net to a depth of 6 meters. This net with strong and elastic multifilament canvas is ideally suited for catching big and active fish. The cells of this net too big to catch small fish. </text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_alcohol">Glass bottles</text>
   <text id="quest_3_7_2">Catch some Nases in the Hidden Creek!</text>
   <text id="str_tutorial_comics_text9">	This is an experience scale! Get experience and receive rewards!	</text>
   <text id="str_ok_sending_error">Ошибка соединения. Попробуйте еще раз.</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_nublsmt_desc">A fantastic example of evolutionary inventions in industrial fishing! Nubler received another upgrade and allows you to catch 2,5 kg fish.</text>
   <text id="str_faq_question5">What do I need different fishing rods for?
    </text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc11_descr_6">Catch [amount] Salmons at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_catching_message5">MAGNIFICENT!</text>
   <text id="halloween_1_desc"> In the night strange creatures wake up in the river... You have to catch them in order to stop scare local people! </text>
   <text id="str_scene_shop_bought">Bought</text>
   <text id="str_fb_text2">Oh, Lord... Finally I've caught what I want!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_12">Winner - Get all Victory River location achievements</text>
   <text id="quest_7_2_desc">A farmer from the lodge near the river invited us politely to partake in fishing... One cannot refuse!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_alga">Alga is the perfect bait for Mirror carp in particular. But don't expect a predator like a pike to be impressed!</text>
   <text id="str_alert_please_select_spining">Please use spinning with spoon-bait.</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_santa">Christmas collection</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc6_descr_5">Catch Chums: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_location_open_sea">Tired of river fish? Bored of fishing from the shore? The time has come to go sea fishing! Invigorating see breezes, salty spray, serenading wash, the calls of seagulls. And, certainly, you could catch a really large fish here!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc10_descr_1">Catch Tilapias: [amount]</text>
   <text id="new_year_10_desc">	It seems like this fish has adapted to living in extreme conditions… Its scientific value will be appreciated at the laboratory!	</text>
   <text id="quest_4_6_2">Catch some White-finned Gudgeons!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_gen_descr_13">Exotics Lover - win all achievements in Amazon location</text>
   <text id="str_shop_info_for_omnivore">For %s omnivore fish</text>
   <text id="str_light">Small</text>
   <text id="str_fish_brand_rotan_descr_imp">Brand Rotan prefers stagnant water and swamps, rivers with muddy bottoms. Brand Rotan reaches a length of 0.8 ft, but the usual size is up to 3, rarely up to 5.5 inches. Brand Rotan is extremely unpretentious and can live and breed in highly polluted water under adverse environmental conditions.</text>
   <text id="og_open_elovyi_shore">We heard a wild roar somewhere in the thickets, very close to us. I am not usually one to run hell for leather – I just needed to brace myself and get ready to face the danger.</text>
   <text id="quest_11_6_2">Catch some Array Scates!</text>
   <text id="new_year_18_2">	Catch a Dorado weighing 10 kg faster than others!	</text>
   <text id="halloween_7_1"> Catch some Arthrodiras! </text>
   <text id="victory_day_2_2">	Endear local residents, throwing some feed in the water.	</text>
   <text id="str_fish_palia_ozern">Lake Paly</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_sosiska">Sausage-fish</text>
   <text id="quest_13_5_1">Catch some Lamperns!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_9">Urgent Research</text>
   <text id="str_lure_gone">Lure slipped!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_8_3">You'll also need some Gold to pay for the journey!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_blesna_usuall_descr">Simple copper spoon designed for reels. Excellent for checking one's talents!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_fun_frogprince_descr">Every girl dreams of meeting her prince! It may be cool to present this crowned frog to any dreamer! For no matter how long it is kissed, it will refuse to turn into a prince again! Because this one escaped from a princess to croak alone in swamps long ago. </text>
   <text id="str_najivka_flavored_bait">It is really hard to overestimate the importance of flavoured bait when you are going to catch a rare fish like an Amur carp</text>
   <text id="str_policy_text3">You may decide to provide us with another person's personal information such as email address so that the person may be invited to join the Service. We use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person that he or she has been invited to join the Service or receive content from the Service. We may disclose such information if required to do so in order to comply with legal process, as described above. </text>
   <text id="str_udochka_bear_light">Medium spinning of the &quot;Bear&quot; series. The price is moderated by high quality and reliability. You may now forget unpleasent sound when your rod is cracking under the weight of fish! The largest bearable fish may even exceed 20 kg, as specified by the manufacturer.</text>
   <text id="quest_11_2">Gift from Guests!</text>
   <text id="quest_15_5_1">Catch some Drytails!</text>
   <text id="quest_4_10">Mountain Lake</text>
   <text id="quest_10_10_3">You'll also need some Gold to pay for the journey!</text>
   <text id="quest_12_2_1">Catch some Chums!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_8_1">Catch some Tankfish.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc4_descr_0">Catch Carps: [amount]</text>
   <text id="victory_day_3">	State of emergency	</text>
   <text id="quest_1_3">	Mythbursters	</text>
   <text id="halloween_3_3"> Catch Thornies on the total weight 2 kg! </text>
   <text id="new_year_14">	Snowy Fish	</text>
   <text id="new_year_14_desc">	Laboratory assistants say there is one more mysterious creature living in these waters, and ask us for help!	</text>
   <text id="quest_7_3_1">Use the Hydra spoonbait.</text>
   <text id="quest_12_2_desc">The forester living nearby has said he'll allow us to fish there only if we surpass his fishing mastery!</text>
   <text id="new_year_8_1">	Catch a Santa-fish weighing 4 kg!	</text>
   <text id="victory_day_10">	Underwater tanks	</text>
   <text id="str_change_day_night_buy">Change</text>
   <text id="str_fish_trairao">Anjumara</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_sahar_descr">Who could guess that cruel predators such as pike and eels would have such a sweet tooth? But it's true! So, always take some sugar with you if you go fishing for those toothy creatures!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_6_1">Catch some Arctic Chars!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_8_2">Catch a Chum Salmon weighing at least 2 kg and become the chosen one!</text>
   <text id="str_fishlist_title">Salvage</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc9_descr_4">Catch Coho Salmons: [amount]</text>
   <text id="quest_15_6_2">Catch an Openerfish weighing 3.2 kg!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_1_2">Catch any fish on the new spot!</text>
   <text id="quest_bonus_1_desc">	To complete this quest you need to perform several tasks:	</text>
   <text id="quest_9_10_3">You'll also need some Gold to pay for the journey!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_interface_reward">Reward:</text>
   <text id="quest_10_5">National Zoo</text>
   <text id="quest_7_1_desc">Wow, that's beautiful! Let's see how welcoming are the fishes, which live there.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_tambakyi_descr">Owing to their excellent sense of smell they can smell fruit ripening on the shore! They'll start swimming around a tree, waiting for ripe fruit to fall. They won't refuse a couple of shellfish either.</text>
   <text id="quest_9_9_2">Catch some Pikes in the Moon Bay!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_2_1">Catch several Graylings!</text>
   <text id="str_location_block_or">OR</text>
   <text id="str_shop_tab_najivki" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Baits</text>
   <text id="str_location_secret_backwater">Night fishing is a special treat. Particularly if you are in the untamed wilderness, sitting on the edge of a serene bay with all the stars of the universe mirrored in the water. There's only the chirping of crickets and the occasional splash of a fish to break the silence</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_banki">Tin cans</text>
   <text id="str_coll_set_koriagi">Figure snags</text>
   <text id="str_location_buy_button">Unlock now</text>
   <text id="quest_12_4_1">Catch some Arctic Salmons!</text>
   <text id="quest_6_9">Zoo Order</text>
   <text id="str_server_gold_title">Attention</text>
   <text id="str_fish_golyan">Minnow</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc9_descr_0">Catch a Tank fish: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_ybiica">Killer-worm</text>
   <text id="str_fish_ribec">Vimba</text>
   <text id="quest_15_3">Bottlers</text>
   <text id="quest_13_2_desc">A local monk alleges he can catch more fish than you, with the God's blessing! We'll see!</text>
   <text id="halloween_8_2"> Catch Amur catfish at least 3.2 kg! </text>
   <text id="str_comics5">It has taken me only twelve hours, and here I am!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc2_descr_4">Catch any fish at least  [weight]</text>
   <text id="str_fish_nase">Nase are typical river fish eating organic remains that have settled on the bottom and various small creatures that crawl on the stony or hard sandy riverbed. The best nutritional conditions are at a medium depth of 0.4-1.8 meters, where the riverbed is covered by an alga carpet. Nase are shoaling fish that inhabit rapidly flowing deep water, often located near bridges.</text>
   <text id="quest_12_8_2">Catch fish weighing 6 kg in total! You'll need something to eat during the journey!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_spining_caplia">Sp. &quot;Heron</text>
   <text id="quest_3_5">Re-stocking!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_51_text">[fish type] are definitely biting - I've caught [total weight] in just a couple of hours! I'll be very surprised if you manage to catch the same!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_sky_gazer">Sky gazers are predatory fish that prefer to swim mainly in the mid waters. They can reach a length of 102cms and weigh up to 9 kg. Sky gazers feed on young crucians and ichs. Their diet includes insect larvae and dayflies during their mass swarming. The mouth of a sky gazer is directed upwards. After reaching 7cm, sky gazers switch to eating fish that have a mainly oblong body shape.</text>
   <text id="quest_4_7_2">Bring some new species for aquariums: Catch some Osmans!</text>
   <text id="str_location_seversky">Seversky Donets</text>
   <text id="quest_1_8_2">Catch Breams.</text>
   <text id="str_fish_baikal_omul_descr">Baikal omul are the most famous species among cisco fish. Twenty thousand years ago polar oceanic omul swam to Baikal through the Arctic Ocean along the river system and they have inhabited this unique lake since the Ice Age. Unlike many other fish, Baikal omul can live both in salted and fresh water.</text>
   <text id="quest_1_6">Rare Species</text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer4">You need different lures and baits to catch different kinds of fish! By combining them, you'll get a lot of catch!
    </text>
   <text id="quest_7_4_2">Catch some Ciscos in the Mountain Lake!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_gaika_desc"> A cheaper equivalent of Hydra spoon. A well polished nut can be as sinkers and spoon at the same time . </text>
   <text id="quest_14_4_desc">A local spoonbaits producer needs some silver to produce special silver baits. We can be of help!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_kizuch">Coho</text>
   <text id="quest_2_2_desc">Urban life has made you meek! You are no match to me when it comes to fishing! Wanna bet?</text>
   <text id="og_open_moon_bay">Night fishing is a particular pleasure, especially when you are in the middle of nowhere, on a quiet bay, the mirrored surface of which reflects the moon and stars. The silence is only broken by the chirr of crickets and rare splashes of water as the fish are biting!</text>
   <text id="quest_14_8_3">You'll also need some Gold to pay for the journey!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_9_2">Catch some Nases!</text>
   <text id="new_year_1_3">	Catch fish weighing 3 kg in total, fishing with Santa!	</text>
   <text id="halloween_4_3"> Catch Rotans on the total weight 2.5 kg! </text>
   <text id="quest_11_5_2">Catch some Peacock Basses!</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc2_descr_9">Catch Rare Barb at least [weight]</text>
   <text id="str_now_available">Now available:</text>
   <text id="quest_5_3_desc">A local living near the lake has lost an exhibit from his collection of shaped snags!</text>
   <text id="quest_2_1_1">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="new_year_7_1">	Catch some Rotans as a gift for Uncle Joe!	</text>
   <text id="str_atlas_record3">My personal record is: %s</text>
   <text id="str_fish_karp">Carp</text>
   <text id="quest_12_5_3">Catch some fish!</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_coins_desc"> A cheaper equivalent of a Worm spoon. The great way to increase the value of small coins - make them something more! </text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc11_descr_7">Catch [amount] White Amurs at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="quest_2_4_desc">Do you remember that I've lost my favourite Teddy bear here last summer... I wonder, what happened to him?</text>
   <text id="quest_7_8_desc">There is a local rumour, which says that only the chosen one can catch the biggest Chum Salmon in this lake! I bet, that's not true!</text>
   <text id="str_uncatched_need_rod">Is required:</text>
   <text id="str_quest_title">Quest:</text>
   <text id="str_fish_beloper_peskar">Whitefin Gudgeon</text>
   <text id="quest_13_3_1">Catch some Gudgeons!</text>
   <text id="str_amulet_proposal_desc_2">+30% weight</text>
   <text id="quest_1_8_1">Catch Grassy Pikes.</text>
   <text id="quest_2_7_2">Catch some Ides!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_2_desc">Wlocal fishermen just laugh at our intention to catch some Eels. Are they really so elusive?</text>
   <text id="quest_2_3_desc">The annual fishing tournament is coming up. Let's show what we're up to, we're here to beat everyone, after all!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_spining_molnia">Sp. &quot;Lightning</text>
   <text id="quest_10_3_1">Cast yout line several times! It will take some doing to get silver!</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_nublsimpl_desc">Classic spinning from the Nubler Series, which has proved itself with time. An excellent model for starting a serious career in the fishing industry. Allows you to catch 2 kg fish!</text>
   <text id="str_athlas_welcomegroup">Go to the community</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_killing_worm">The killer-worm is so deadly that only the most dangerous and experienced fish dare to try eating it! Even when stuck on a hook, it can still sometimes catch fish stupid enough to swim too close!</text>
   <text id="quest_15_4">Barrelfish</text>
   <text id="quest_1_8">Fishing in the Night</text>
   <text id="str_fish_sazan">Common Carp</text>
   <text id="victory_day_8_desc">	It's time to unite all efforts before the attack! Collect all types of fish soldiers in one squad to make it invincible!	</text>
   <text id="quest_11_8_2">Catch some fish weighing at least 3 kg.</text>
   <text id="quest_9_1">Mysterious Lake</text>
   <text id="str_udochka_spark_desc">A pretty strong rod for those who don't want their first big fish to get off the hook.</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc12_descr_1">Catch Breams: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_shop_tab_prikormki" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="32">Lures</text>
   <text id="str_30th_reset">Reset XP</text>
   <text id="quest_15_2_3">Catch the brewer's bottle!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_brand_rotan_descr">Brand Rotan prefers stagnant water and swamps, rivers with muddy bottoms. Brand Rotan reaches a length of 24 cm, but the usual size is up to 8, rarely up to 14 cm. Brand Rotan is extremely unpretentious and can live and breed in highly polluted water under adverse environmental conditions.</text>
   <text id="str_spin_free_now">Free spin</text>
   <text id="str_shop_info_type_unique">unique</text>
   <text id="quest_7_5_1">Use the Nubler Smart rod.</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_choco">Chocolate</text>
   <text id="quest_5_3_3">Catch a shaped snug!</text>
   <text id="halloween_6_1"> Catch some Humpback Salmon! </text>
   <text id="str_faq_answer18">You can buy all you need for fishing from the Shop, which is accessed by clicking on the button in the lower left corner of the screen. Also, you can get some lures and baits by completing quests.
    </text>
   <text id="quest_2_9_3">Catch Nases weighing 3.75 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_3_4_1">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_tushenka">Canned meat</text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc1_descr_8">Catch [amount] Common Carps at least [weight] each</text>
   <text id="str_najivka_gaika"> Nut </text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc13_descr_2"> Catch Catfish: [amount] </text>
   <text id="quest_5_2_desc">A farmer living near the lake has given us a wonderful cake as a welcome gift... We should reciprocate!</text>
   <text id="quest_7_1_3">Cast your line several times!</text>
   <text id="str_fish_white_eye">White eye prefers waters with fast and moderate stream, avoiding flood waters. During the feeding keeps in small flocks during the breeding and wintering areas is collected in large flocks. It feeds on aquatic insect larvae, small mollusks, algae and zooplankton. White eye is sensitive to pollution, and can be found only in clean waters. </text>
   <text id="str_ach_loc3_descr_2">Catch Bream: [amount]</text>
   <text id="str_shop_inapp_confirm_title">Not enough a little bit</text>
   <text id="new_year_2_desc">Santa told the Spirit of Christmas is extremely weak… If we don't take measures, the holidays won't come!</text>
   <text id="quest_5_1_2">Catch fish weighing 15 kg in total!</text>
   <text id="quest_10_5_desc">The National Zoo asks you to catch some rare local fish!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_0_text" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="18">Use lures to attract more fish, and catch an excellent bream</text>
   <text id="str_quest_0_task0" fontname="Marker Felt" fontsize="17">Catch [amount] bream</text>
   <text id="str_pdkormka_suhariki_descr">If you bait a fishing spot with crackers, large species of fish such as bream or roach will bite more often.</text>
   <text id="str_tournaments_leave_now">Leave now</text>
   <text id="quest_5_10_3">Spend some gold to buy equipment: we'll need it!</text>
   <text id="quest_13_6_1">Catch some Royal Fish in the Northern Donets!</text>
   <text id="str_quest_finished">Ты завершил задание </text>
</locale>
